Good morning, afternoon, whatever it is.
It's Tuesday.
You know what that means?
It means Domino's has 50% off in my hometown, so I'll probably get that.
But also probably not, because it's still kind of expensive, even if it's 50% off.
Wait a minute, it is Tuesday, right?
It is Tuesday.
Nice.
I actually recently found out that there was a Domino's where I live, and I thought for the longest time that that wasn't an American thing.
But apparently we have it here too.
There's that.
I've got more information in a couple hours about that.
Pizza on a Tuesday?
Ah, I know it should be tacos, right?
There's actually a taco truck nearby, but it's unbelievably expensive.
It's like 115 kroners for three kind of tiny tacos.
To translate that into U.S.
dollars.
Let me see here.
What is that?
It's like $18, man.
For three tiny tacos.
It is unbelievably expensive, so I almost never do that.
Yeah, it's insane.
I don't even get full from it.
That's not something you should do.
It's too expensive.
I thought Denmark was euro.
We are part of Europe, but we have not adopted the euro, the coin.
We have our own currency, and we like it that way.
The only time it would make sense is back when the coin offer was one euro at McDonald's, you know?
Because our coin offer was 10 kroners, so that was like three kroners at the time more expensive.
So, at that specific time, it would have made sense for us to go euro, you know?
Otherwise, it wouldn't be called a coin offer.
Oh, man.
It's time for some Minecraft again.
It's been a while, huh?
Dude, I feel so good today.
It's one of those days.
Guys, I can't wait to just get in to my Minecraft world, do some mining, some crafting, some creating.
And I also remember that I kind of made a big discovery last time.
Kind of forgot what it was, though, so...
We're gonna have to rediscover that!
And it's like a little surprise waiting, you know?
You don't know what you're gonna get.
But I know it's gonna be good.
Sorry, I had to mute there.
I just did the nastiest burp of all time.
Even Jackie, like, perked up and looked at me like, Are you serious, bro?
It's okay, Jackie.
I muted in time, so you wouldn't have to endure that.
Diabolical cliffhanger back then.
You're right.
I am a demon.
I am... No, wait.
Diabolical?
That's like Di... Diablo?
What's the singular for Di... Diabolical?
It's, uh...
It's a demon?
I think it's demon, guys.
That is definitely, like, uh...
Related to demons, right?
Also, my cam...
I mean, not my cam, my...
I don't know why I said cam.
My glasses...
I'm mixing up my day jobs here.
My glasses are dirty.
Right now.
I gotta clean them.
I can't see shit.
Oh god, I hope nobody finds my campsite.
Oh, man.
How y'all doing today, huh?
Are you doing good on a Tuesday?
It's been years.
I know.
I'm sorry about that.
I need some time off.
Amazing?
Great!
Me too.
The ferns?
You're doing good on a Tuesday?
I love asking that way.
Are you feeling good on a Tuesday?
First day with no heat here in Greece.
We finally got some wind.
That's nice.
We've been clear of the heat for a while now here in Denmark, so that's nice.
It was definitely kind of crazy.
And I managed to survive very nicely, though, because I have the AC.
I haven't even had it on for a while now.
But I can't...
I almost can't wait for the next summer just to activate it again.
And just sit there and freeze to death while everybody else just dies from heat.
Best feeling ever.
Today has concluded my classes for my first semester.
Very nice!
Congratulations.
What is the soundtrack from?
It is from Expedition 33.
A Claire Obscure.
Just one Claire Obscure.
Like, this track is some of the best shit I've ever heard.
In a game that is, for me otherwise, not very great.
But that's me.
And I'm very much the outlier.
That's a hot take.
I get it.
You can roast me on the fire.
It's okay.
Fight me.
Sounds like Isaac music.
Yeah, actually.
Kinda.
I can see that.
There's definitely some similarities.
I can see it.
Petition for Oliver to put song title on screen.
We actually had a period where I did that.
But there was some problems with it.
It was kind of an annoyance, actually.
Because the way I had it made back then was that...
It would, you know, register the song name from Foo.
Foo Bar that I have running.
But not everything came from Foo Bars.
It was like...
I had to...
It was just a mess.
It didn't work very well.
And sometimes it wouldn't register it.
It was just a mess.
I'm sorry.
But you know what?
Not having the song title there actually drives engagement.
Because there's people in the comments on YouTube going, Guys, what's the song?
You know, then someone responds and boom, we have comments.
It's all calculated.
Even here on stream.
People are like, what's the song?
Huh?
Not bad.
Someone also said in the KSP VOD on YouTube that I should change the title to Astrophysicist Plays and I would get like a billion views.
So now I did it.
And let's see if he's right.
Let's see if a billion views are coming in because of that.
I've never been a fan of that sort of, I don't know, title like that.
Something about it rubs me the wrong way, you know?
Because it gives people this expectation, I guess, that I'm going to be this super amazing smart guy and I can't do any wrong, you know what I mean?
And I don't want to set that expectation either.
Because that's definitely not what it's going to be.
It's going to be me fucking crashing rockets and killing kerbals.
Just as much as the next guy, you know?
Extra Astrophysicist Plays, I like that.
That's cool.
I mean, technically I still have the title, right?
But still.
Clickbait is beneath me?
It's not really.
I do clickbait sometimes.
Sometimes I'll write something like, uh, situation gone wrong, cops called, and stuff like that.
Even though no cops were actually called.
I'm lying about that.
I just straight up lie.
I say cops were called, no mention of any cops at all.
But I say it.
That's true.
There's actually videos with that title.
You can find them.
There's also this, yeah, the silksong thumbnail.
That's, I was just thinking about that, Penguin.
The silksong thumbnail with the title, it was something like, uh, uh, what was it?
Oh god, I, I forgot what it was, but it was like, leaning towards something lewd, especially with the thumbnail, it was very clickbaity.
And the worst part is, it got way more views than all the other videos.
Damn it, man.
But hey, you know, it works.
Uh, YonahKittyCat, first time chatter, what's up?
Don't normally say anything in chat, but I've been watching your VODs since you first did the Minecraft line series, and it's genuinely the best background noise ever.
I've just been binging random VODs and it boosts productivity like 10x.
That's interesting.
It actually boosts your productivity.
I would have thought it would, you know, make it worse, because you're being distracted by all the shenanigans.
But I'm glad you like it, YonahKitty.
Thank you for saying that.
Appreciate it.
I think your thumbnails really elevate the experience.
Dude, I'm actually kind of...
Like, obviously I really enjoy making the thumbnails.
Like, I shit you not.
Some games, I have literally spent over 50 hours on a thumbnail.
Like, multiple days.
From morning to night.
I'm not shitting you.
And the worst part is, I could have just done something way more clickbaity and easy.
But I really enjoy it, you know?
Like, I'm kind of sacrificing clicks for these thumbnails that I made.
Which ones?
Oh, let me think.
Which one was the worst that took so long?
Oh, it was probably...
Slay the Princess was one of them.
That one took forever to make.
And also Animal Well.
Animal Well was...
I think that one took two days.
Like, over 40 hours for sure.
I went through, like, 10 different variations and ideas.
And I didn't like any of them.
Until I ended up with something that I actually liked.
Uh...
Let me see.
Silent Hill 2 also took a long time.
That one really...
Made me pull my hair out at certain points.
Slay the Spire was also one of them.
Oh, and of course...
I think the one I spent the most time on of all the videos...
Can you guess which one it is?
It's not a recent one.
It's not Outer Wilds, actually.
Outer Wilds kind of came together quite nicely.
It's a game you probably wouldn't expect at all.
Uh...
I'm trying to remember the name of it now, actually.
How can...
Why can't I remember the name?
I'm trying to find the thumbnail on my...
YouTube right now.
God damn.
Oh, yeah.
This one.
It's Dredge.
Dredge took...
So fucking long.
Because I really like the idea of having, you know...
Custom...
Uh...
Thumbnails for the different parts of the game.
Ooh, that was...
That was a rough one, man.
But yeah, Dredge.
That one took the longest, for sure.
If you were to make a game, what game would it be?
Something like...
Something related to space.
I would probably say...
A mix between Elite Dangerous...
Um...
And...
No, it would probably just be Elite Dangerous, but with, like, unlimited money.
You know?
Like...
Interiors on Spacecraft.
Way more, like, objectives.
Or...
Oh!
No, no, no.
Hold on.
World of Starcraft.
I would hire all the old guys from Blizzard.
And if they said, Nah, I'm too old.
I'm not making games anymore.
I'm not...
I'm just gonna throw money at them.
Like...
Make it!
World of Starcraft.
With the same design.
Uh...
Goals as the original vanilla World of Warcraft.
Holy shit.
That would be it.
Don't even know what it's gonna look like, but I just want it.
You know?
What do you mean I don't like Project Hail Mary?
I do like that movie.
Oh my god.
Made by an astrophysicist.
Yeah, exactly.
You said you weren't impressed?
Well, it's not my favorite movie ever.
It was...
It was okay.
But that's it, you know?
It was a good movie.
Project Hail Mary or Interstellar?
Oh, Interstellar.
10 out of 10 times.
Rocky.
I actually don't even remember that one.
It's been so long.
But I...
I did like it.
Oh my god.
There's something in my throat.
What is happening to me?
I need to drink more.
Yeah, I'm watching Jacksepticeye right now play Detroit Become Human.
There's already stuff that I haven't seen that is happening in that.
So...
I'm already experiencing other paths, you know?
You like superhero stuff?
Not that much.
I really liked the Dark Knights trilogy.
That was a good one.
But like Superman...
Not really.
If they make a good one, I guess I will like it.
Okay, guys.
It's time for some Minecraft.
Let's bring in the music.
Wait, did I?
Fucking Minecraft crashed!
There's something about...
When you leave Minecraft open in the background, it just crashes, man.
I've had this happen multiple times.
Let me launch it again.
I'm launching it via Prism, so I don't know if it's related to that.
Pretty sure it didn't happen before I did this.
There we go.
And you can't see it, of course.
But now you can.
There we go.
Last time played...
Oh my god.
Dude, it's been like three weeks.
Well, almost.
Two weeks.
Whoa.
Whoa!
It just loaded really slowly.
I guess it's been a while.
Even the world is like...
Oh yeah, right.
What were we doing?
Wait, I remember this.
Why did I do this?
Oh, slime!
We were doing slimes.
I remember having an issue with slimes where I needed a lot of slimes.
And the reason I needed slimes was to make glue.
And I figured out how to make slimes from something.
Right.
You just color dough.
That's what it was.
Some kind of blob.
First things first, though.
Oh yeah, and the reason I wanted glue in the first place was to make trains.
I remember this now.
But I think I ran out of tracks.
We needed train tracks.
Hold on.
Tracks.
Okay.
Stone slabs and iron nuggets.
So we need iron.
Or sink.
Both can work.
That's what I was doing.
Right, I was doing the whole railway.
I remember now.
It's coming back.
First we clear the inventory, though.
I don't need any of this right now.
And lime dye.
Let's put that in here.
Although I...
I think I already made a bunch of glue.
So I don't need any more right now.
Fuck.
Oh man, I feel good just playing this right now.
This is just...
Something about Minecraft, you know?
When you get into the game and you're like...
You see everything you've made.
It's a nice feeling.
It's like a second home, you know?
No, in a way.
Dirt!
Put that in here.
And this one here.
What was that?
Was that an animal grazing?
Oh, it's...
It's this up here.
It's the harvesting technique.
Speaking of animals grazing.
Let's go graze the animals ourselves.
This needs to happen once in a while.
There we go.
Make lots of babies so we can slaughter them.
I think the food situation at this point is solved.
We never have issues with food anymore.
Come on, nobody?
Nobody?
There we go.
Don't follow me.
Nice.
They're gonna produce a lot of offspring.
Right for slaughtering.
And we have the planks.
You know, it's weird.
At this point in Minecraft, it's like I don't even look at what's on the screen.
It's like I'm some sort of machine that just analyzes the pixels.
And I'm like, okay, I'm here.
I need to put in wood.
I know that it's over here, so I don't even look where I'm going.
I'm just sort of estimating.
It's like a percentage-based statistics thing where I just go in a certain direction.
It's hard to explain.
Like, I'm not even thinking.
I'm just doing.
That probably didn't make any sense, what I just said.
But trust me, there's something there.
And it's really weird.
I guess this would be construction?
Yeah.
Actually, give me these.
And these.
And this...
No, this one stays.
Put that there.
Do I have anything in this?
Nothing.
Okay.
So, obviously, the next step is to make a lot of train tracks.
That's the next thing.
And all we need is stone slaps and sink nuggets.
And I think we already have the setup going.
Slaps.
Give me a lot.
Actually, we can maybe take more.
There we go.
Put this back.
Don't eat this bread.
Oh, that's right.
We got elytra.
But the problem is, we cannot use it yet.
Unless we get mending.
That's why I needed to kidnap villagers.
Maybe we need to do that first, actually.
Hmm.
Let me think.
We needed to make lead for this.
Lead and boats, right?
That was the trick.
And now we have slime balls!
Oh, it's perfect.
Strings.
That was also a bottleneck, I guess.
Slime balls are over here.
Oh, I may not have enough here.
Hmm.
Lead.
Oh!
It makes two.
Okay, that's good.
Fantastic.
Then we need a boat.
I think I'm gonna start doing this first.
Like, we're gonna get a villager here.
We're gonna make him make a mending for us.
And we can do that by just re-rolling his stats or whatever.
It's gonna be nice.
Yeah.
Boat.
And then I'm gonna deposit all this nugget stuff back here.
That's the plan.
Yeah.
Dude, I love the design on these rails.
Look at how smooth this looks, man.
When it's, like, diverging like that.
So cool.
You can't walk on them, though.
It's just visual, it seems.
It's kind of half-fake, you know?
But it's not fake for the train.
The train will obey.
Everything else, though, doesn't look like it.
What's happening here?
Just constantly cutting some wheels.
Weird.
And this one was to make...
I forgot what that was.
But what we need to do is to just have two presses, which we have.
So we can actually turn this into what we need.
Give me this.
Oh, wait.
Wait, why did I make this again?
Was that to make...
Hold on.
Powdered.
Oh!
Oh, that's right.
Sturdy sheet.
Makes train casing.
The thing is, though, we don't need more train casings right now, I don't think.
Like, train casings?
We're good on that, you know?
It's the...
Tracks?
That's the problem.
Okay.
So basically, we need to fill this up with stone slabs now and put...
Ah, wait a minute.
No, these need to be hands.
Don't they?
Track.
Yeah, they're hands.
Hands and then a press.
Okay.
Oh, I already had this set up over here.
So we don't have to replace, we can just use what we have.
That's actually great.
I think I have more hands.
Deployer, I mean.
It's the word for that.
You know what I mean.
Man, this house is really growing on me.
I was not a fan of it at first.
Like, super duper fan, but now I think I'm a mega fan.
In fact, I'm a giga fan.
Great house.
Of course, you know, the storage situation is not ideal.
It's kind of funny how my vanilla world with storage is much better than this one.
But I also spent more time in it, so it makes sense.
Deployer.
Oh, we have some train tracks here.
Nice.
Three there.
Actually, I just need two.
Wonderful.
Now we're gonna put everything in.
We're just gonna let it run for ten years, so that we have a million tracks.
And while that runs...
While that runs...
What am I gonna do?
Oh, I'm gonna go kidnap people.
That's right.
So here...
Oh, I guess we only needed one of these.
Oh, that's right.
I'm sneaking, too.
Oops.
Shit.
Give me that.
It's a little finicky, this.
You gotta sort of...
There we go.
Ah!
Overstressed.
Disconnect.
Whoa!
My game just lagged like crazy.
Okay.
And then at the end, we need a press.
I'm just gonna take one of these.
Am I, though?
Am I?
I feel like I shouldn't cannibalize like this.
Like, if we want a sustainable future, we need to make sure that everything just works.
And we don't need to move things around.
Get a proper one.
Let's see.
Don't see one here.
Oh, we have a bunch of deployers here, too.
In fact, let's just put these here, then.
Man.
Damn it.
Press.
Oh, that's the one that takes a block of iron.
It's expensive.
Hey, I can actually make it.
It's no problem.
Although, we do need to blast.
This was washing, right?
Yeah.
Okay, fine.
Give me that.
I mean, obviously, we would have a blaster.
A, uh...
Like, a, um...
A fan, you know?
But it's okay.
For now, it's okay.
We need nine.
Nice.
And casing.
And what was the other one?
A shaft.
Just a shaft.
Whoops.
Okay.
Double check.
Do I need anything else?
So, we got two hands.
We got a press.
We got the belt.
I think we're good.
Now, this thing also needs to be activated for real at some point.
I gotta make it into a proper digging machine.
Don't get cut.
We need to fix this by having more power.
We take these now.
Ah, but here's the thing.
I could just manually put them in their hands.
But we kind of don't want to do that.
Ideally...
I mean, for now, it's okay.
It's not perfect, but, you know.
There you go.
And then, over here...
Put in all of this.
Oh, yeah.
We're tracking now.
I gotta go sneeze and blow my nose while this happens.
Be right back.
Okay, there we go.
Now, the question is...
We're gonna make one set of tracks for every two nuggets.
Right?
Yeah, just one.
So, really...
It's just gonna take a lot of iron.
Or sink.
But I do have these two as well.
The thing is, this is gonna be consumed so fast.
Like, 34 tracks is nothing.
Yeah.
I mean, we could just go on a quick little mining trip.
Man, I forgot.
Did my...
Did my shit blow up?
I made, like, a huge miner in the nether.
Remember?
And...
Oh, wait.
I remember now.
I died down there.
I was being a little bitch.
Too greedy.
And then I lost it all.
And what happened to my digging machine?
I think it may have just...
I actually forgot about that.
Give me this.
As soon as this has run out...
There you go.
That was perfectly timed, man.
And that's...
Oh, we also have this.
Ooh, nice.
Actually, I can just do that.
Uh, wait.
Do this.
Okay, we're getting a lot of tracks here.
I feel like maybe I should bring this back to my home.
I don't like this chest being here.
It's just confusing.
Maybe we put the...
crafting thing over here.
Maybe it's also time to finally encase this, uh...
factory.
With some walls.
Wait, what?
Oh, okay.
I think I'm just gonna go lay down some tracks.
While that's working.
I do like looking at it, though, when it's going, but still.
Oh, wait a sec, wait a sec.
I was trying to make this thing dig.
But it wasn't very, uh, practical.
That was the issue.
It's better to just have a manual digging machine, I think.
To dig it beforehand, and then, uh...
Yeah, that's right.
True.
Also, I'm just getting distracted left and right again and again here.
Like, originally I was gonna go kidnap villagers, and now I'm sort of thinking about this.
Holy shit.
It's really easy to get distracted in this game.
All the stuff we don't need.
Put them in.
I almost was about to say, let's make the blaster now, since we have this fan.
But, that's just another distraction.
We can't do it.
Food there.
Why did we need the villagers?
Mending.
Right.
Let's go get villagers now.
Uh, we sleep first.
Go to bed.
This is the plan.
One thing at a time.
Don't get overwhelmed.
I'm just gonna take a quick trip to the factory and deposit this last, uh...
nugget.
That I have.
That's all.
There you go.
Wonderful.
And the rest is good.
Let's go.
Now, there's a village back there.
And it doesn't really matter who I kidnap.
I just need to kidnap, like, two people or something.
Why two and not one?
Well, simply because, uh...
I may as well take more than one, right?
Since I'm taking the trip anyway.
I'm trying to think what other villagers I may want.
So we definitely have one for enchanting.
In fact, we could have two people for enchanting.
One making mending, and the other one making something else.
That I really need.
What else do I really need?
Hmm.
Maybe just something like smite.
Five.
You know?
Something really solid.
So even if I were to lose my tools, I can easily get it back.
Also, I'm going west right now.
Even brought a compass.
Oh, that's right.
We need to relocate this compass.
But there was a complication with that last time.
I couldn't really do it for some reason.
I think I didn't have the materials needed to make the thing I need to make.
Which is unfortunate.
Okay.
The villagers should be right there.
Wonderful.
There's actually kind of a convenient little river here.
Haters will say this is not efficient.
But they don't know me.
There's actually more to this than it seems.
There we go.
Look at that.
I didn't even have to get out of the boat.
That's efficiency, people.
It's like when I take a train to my parents, there's either the option of going direct without any stops or like switches to another train, but it takes way longer.
But I will always pick that, because I hate switching trains.
I like going in, just sitting in my seat, fall asleep, and wake up when I'm there.
You know what I mean?
Okay, who shall I take?
Maybe I should just pop up during the middle of the night, you know, and take people out of their homes.
Oh, wow!
Fuck that.
Stop.
You are a cartographer.
Congratulations.
You are not what I need.
So you get to, I was about to say live, but you all get, what's happening in here?
What are you doing with these people?
Huh?
You're a leather man?
Leather, lederhosen.
Okay, these guys are unemployed.
We're taking them.
Ah, wait, I can't do that.
We have to do this?
That's right.
Get in the boat.
Oh, right.
I have to do this.
That's how that works.
Sir, would you like to come with me?
Don't, don't walk in, don't walk in there.
Oh, are you a blacksmithy?
You are.
I'm gonna say you're not, actually.
What do you think of that?
Get in.
Wait, you can't have two people in a boat?
Is that, is that right?
Why do I remember that being a thing?
Well, shit, I gotta make another boat.
It's actually no problem.
Like that, and then we do...
There we go, baby!
And then we do that, and now we're cooking.
Actually, I need another boat.
We're not done yet.
Because this is my boat.
All right, guys.
Off we go.
That was actually so not painful.
It just sort of worked.
Oh, wait.
Maybe it's better if I don't go on a boat yet.
Oh, this is gonna be pain with the water!
Because I can't get out of the water again.
This is the problem.
With kidnapping, you know?
I have to, I have to cut a path.
It's like, uh...
That dude from that movie cutting through the jungle with the machete, you know?
That's me right now.
Don't go to the...
Damn it, man!
Unless I can jump?
Can I jump you out of there?
Okay, wait.
Never mind.
We're actually totally cooking, then.
Come here.
We're going swimming.
For some reason, I thought it couldn't work on water, but...
Here we are.
That has never been a thing.
Like, all the time.
That is recent, you know?
Soon we'll be on the open water, and...
It's gonna be easy.
My turn.
Go!
Did that break?
Why did I break?
Feels so random, doesn't it?
Also, this music?
Is that...
I wonder if that's from creative.
I don't recognize this.
This seems new.
Oh, wait.
He's...
Oh, he's on the shitty path.
Look at that.
That's what's happening here.
Now we're cooking, man.
Cooking with Diesel.
In fact, I'm so confident, I'm not even gonna look back.
I'm not gonna look back once on this entire trip, and you'll see.
This is legitimately, like, one of the harder challenges in this game.
You know, getting the world record for beating the game?
Nothing.
But trying to kidnap villagers without looking at them?
That's a challenge.
Watch me do this.
I refuse to look back.
Looking back means living in the past.
That's not what I'm about.
I'm about the present, baby.
And the future.
In fact, I recognize their voices.
So I'll know if I fuck it up, you know?
Wait, my hope is right there!
We could have swam all the way!
That's fantastic.
For some reason, I thought we had to walk quite a bit.
But this is very nice.
I took a huge detour by walking across that mountain.
Here's where the trouble starts, okay?
Here's where the trouble starts.
I can't look back, so we gotta jump like this.
I think they're both with me.
I gotta clear a path.
Keep jumping in case they have not exited the water yet.
What just happened there?
Keep jumping!
Are you guys with me?
Can you feel it?
In fact, this may be the tech.
The jumping tech.
Oh, but wait.
We are in unknown territory because we currently have train tracks.
We don't know how that interacts.
I gotta chop this down.
Here we go.
Keep jumping.
And...
You ready?
Are those my slaves?
I mean, villagers?
They are...
Before I set them down, though.
We're gonna have to do something here.
Stay there.
I gotta go make a lectern.
Okay.
Bookshelf and slabs.
Easy.
Maybe easy.
Let's...
Oh, wait.
Did I put that in wood?
We got slabs here.
Uh...
Boosh.
Boof.
Bookshelf.
It's books and...
Shelves.
That makes sense.
Do I even have books?
Oh my god!
Do I have books?
I...
Have a lot!
Incredible.
Time for the shelves.
Just one, I guess.
Okay, you ready for this?
Wait a sec, though.
Hold up.
We could have issues here.
Remember the problems we had.
Earlier on with this sort of thing.
We cannot let these guys near any of my other shit.
We need to bring them all the way out to the boons.
The boonies.
Do not fall in that hole.
I will scream if you do.
But quietly.
Come over here.
Don't you...
Dare!
Oh my god, okay, fine.
Hey, I wonder if they can stay in the boat when I put the lectern in their mouth.
That way they don't wander around, you know?
Maybe if they're close enough.
Okay, so watch this.
Move this a little bit.
I don't think so.
But let's see.
Where you going?
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Okay, it's not working.
Let's try the other guy.
See if he's willing to cooperate.
Dude, is it me or is this music, like, really loud?
The lectern!
Stupid-ass villagers.
Maybe I need to release them and then lectern first.
After, I mean.
Let me try...
So this is the plan.
Boom!
Okay, where are they going?
This is like that one movie where the people just wander to this specific spot, you know?
Okay, I don't trust this.
Ah, nah- Oh, shit.
You know what?
Nope.
Go to bed.
We're just going to have to deal with these waves after waves after waves.
Ah.
Are they...
Oh, I thought they were fighting him.
Okay, okay.
They're just sitting in the boat together.
K-I-S-S-I-N-G.
Wait, wait, wait a minute.
This guy is a zombie now!
Wait a sec.
We need to...
We need to cure him.
With an apple.
And we have to weaken him.
We have to weaken him.
Uh, you know what?
Um, we gotta bring this guy...
I don't want this guy to turn.
I just want you in my home.
Tied up in my basement.
Like, I mean...
It's for your own safety, okay?
There's nothing else to it.
Don't overthink this.
I need you back here.
Come here.
There you go.
Stay there.
I'll come for you later.
Okay, so I don't even need to look at the achievement.
I know what to do.
We need, uh, Potion of Weakness.
Uh, uh...
Oh, God.
Potion of Weakness.
I think that was...
Spider...
Eye?
I think?
I need to see this.
Wait, do I even have an apple?
I do, but wait a minute.
We needed, like, a golden apple, right?
Golden...
Actually, okay, I'm gonna read the achievement.
Da-da-da-da-da.
Show me the thing.
Oh, it may not be in here.
Minecraft.
Weaken and then cure a zombie villager.
Yeah, golden apple.
Damn.
That's a lot of gold ingots.
But, uh, you know.
It's fine.
First, we do...
I guess I'll grab some water.
Do I have any nearby?
I forgot if we store water.
Maybe out here.
There we go.
We may have to make it into a splash potion also, by the way.
Man, I wish I had my old notepad from season two.
Oh, that's not even the right one.
Okay, well, we put in the water.
There we go.
Three.
I think we start by making this awkward.
Like that.
And then after that...
We have to make it into a splash.
And we do that with a powder.
It's not redstone.
It is...
It could be blast powder, actually.
Could also be the glowstone.
Let me see here.
Or what...
What is it?
The powder?
Hold on.
What's that called?
Gunpowder.
Right.
I think this is it.
Before we mess it up, let's just try on one.
Wait, I forgot the order.
Maybe we need to do this last, actually.
Hold on.
I think it's last.
So, first...
If I'm even right about the eye.
Okay, it's working.
This could be it.
We actually need to write this down.
And there's also new potions in Create.
So, we have to really keep track of all this.
In fact, I think I hate this thing here.
Do we need...
Oh, this one we did.
Nice.
This one we did.
Did.
Kinda did.
Dude, we did all of this.
This is great.
Why can't I delete these?
Ah, there we go.
Okay.
So, let's see here.
Shit!
Wait, that's poison.
Uh, wait.
We can't...
Oh, no.
Is it Ghast here?
Let's just write this down.
God damn it.
Awkward...
With...
Um...
Oh, man.
Oh.
Uh...
Spider eye...
Becomes...
Uh...
Poison.
Okay.
Awkward with...
Ghast here.
I'm gonna really quickly fix this up here.
There's one.
Oh, what about glowstone dust?
Oh, we know magma cream.
You can write that down.
Here comes fire protection.
That's easy.
Let's see what that one did.
Potion of regeneration!
Sweet.
Not what I need, though, but, uh, you know.
I'll take it.
Ghast here.
I've got slimeball if that did any...
Okay, that does not do anything.
That doesn't do anything?
That is surprising.
Really thought that would do something.
Oh, wait, wait, wait!
I remember, I remember, I remember!
We need to ferment this shit!
Uh, how do I do that?
Sugar, right?
Brown mushroom and sugar.
Ooh, I have one!
No mushrooms, though!
Could be...
Oh!
Never mind, I got it.
Oh, wait, we gotta make this first.
This is it.
Fuck!
Wait, there's something with the fermented spider eye.
Wait, what, why doesn't that work?
There's something with this.
Okay, I actually remember one other.
With...
Uh...
I think it's golden carrot.
Night vision.
Which I actually need a lot of.
And I kinda need to start farming carrots.
That is, uh, kind of a big deal.
Night vision potions, fire protection potions, and...
Yeah, well, those two are the main ones that I just need to have on...
on hand, you know?
For...
for expeditions and stuff.
That's the main thing.
Uh, oh my god.
I...
I forgot about the...
There's something with this...
Forgot what it was.
Um...
I guess I can just...
Hey, let's try some new stuff.
We got pulp now.
Pulp sounds like something I'd like to drink, right?
Okay, I can't put it in.
Because we know there's new potions.
I'm actually kind of excited about that.
What about a cardboard potion?
Ah, that's probably...
Oh, wait, I remember one now.
I think cobblestone.
It was cobblestone, or maybe just stone.
One of these did something.
Okay, it must be stone, then.
Uh, give me just normal stone.
Yep!
I don't think it's gonna make what I want, but it's gonna make something else.
That could be cool.
Such a random thing to put in a potion, you know?
Let me just put some stone in there.
What about dirt?
Should I make a dirt potion?
Drink it up?
Slurp it up?
Potion of infestation.
Awkward with...
Uh, stone.
Potion of...
Infestation, eh?
Very good.
I feel like this is definitely doing something.
What about just standard old sugar?
Just the sugar water.
We can try that.
That's made from cane.
And cane is something I maybe have.
Or not.
In any case, let's make...
a golden apple.
Get this away from me.
So now we have that ready.
For the villager.
Oh, I should also bring the other guys, so they don't somehow die.
Because, uh, these guys, they're kind of important to me.
Okay.
Actually, just one of them.
The other one can fuck off.
This zombie right here can...
You know what, actually?
Maybe...
Maybe it's good to have a zombie in a boat.
Think about it.
Yo!
Okay.
You ready for some crazy tech?
I'm gonna create a little hole.
Like that hole here, for example.
I'm gonna put the boat in there.
With only the zombie.
Right?
Then when I kidnap villagers, and I...
You know, if they misbehave or something.
I throw them in the hole.
What happens?
They're gonna automatically go in the boat.
They're gonna be in proximity to the zombie.
Get turned into a zombie villager.
And we can...
Whoa.
I got too close.
And then we can do stuff with them.
What do you think about that?
It's much better than just waiting for a zombie to show up, and hopefully have them...
You know, infect the guy.
Like I once did.
That was a horrible way to do it.
For now, I'm just gonna put these in a little enclosure over here.
Until I need them.
It's actually so smart.
Holy shit.
Give me the lead.
He took the lead!
Okay, you can keep it.
That's fine.
Keep the lead, damn it.
Whatever.
Let me fence you in.
You bastard.
You ain't going nowhere.
They're gonna make annoying noises, though.
That's the problem, right?
Boom.
We got them.
I may...
I'm kind of sad I have them so close.
They're gonna make annoying noises.
I don't like that.
But, you know...
It's fine.
Golden ingots.
Don't need that right now.
Don't need the books either.
Or this one.
Clean up that inventory.
Spider-Eye.
Oh, wait!
There was something!
I remember now.
We needed to make a certain potion first.
And then add fermented spider-eye.
Oh, there's also the little pufferfish.
Cuttlefish!
That also made something.
This guy.
This could be it, actually.
Uh...
Did I run out of potions?
Damn it.
Damn
it.
In fact, just...
Oh, I ran out of space.
Should have thought about that.
Do-do-do-do-do-do.
Don't wash me.
Wash my belly.
And, and, and, and...
Also that one.
In fact, let's do...
Three at a time?
No, just one.
Just one.
No, we can make them all awkward first.
I like that.
Good start.
Now they become awkward.
Then we have this guy.
Dude, it's all coming together here.
It really is, like...
We got the enchantments.
We killed the dragon.
Trains are on the horizon.
Uh, night vision is coming in, you know?
Like, it's...
Oof.
Fantastic.
Okay, pufferfish!
That's gonna do something.
Not sure what, though.
But it'll do something.
Uh, gunpowder.
I'm pretty sure that does make splash.
So I feel like we should try that with this.
Right!
That's what that did.
Actually, that makes so much sense.
Let me just confirm this.
Okay.
So we have...
We're gonna rebuild...
Oh my god.
We're already so far ahead here.
With...
Pufferfish.
That's one word, I think.
Gives me...
Potion of...
Uh...
Water breathing.
Which is written like that, isn't it?
And now it's splash!
Any...
Potion...
With...
Uh...
What was it?
Gunpowder.
Splash potion.
Cool.
Not what we need, though.
Still.
It's like...
The one thing I need is eluding me right now.
Which is...
Just typical, isn't it?
Every time, man.
Awkward, awkward.
I'm gonna make a couple more awkwards here.
Where's my...
Water...
There we go.
Water, water, water.
Good to have that.
This apple in there.
And this one.
Um...
Why am I...
E-exotic!
Ooh.
Uh...
That is a construction...
And water bucket.
I'm actually gonna make a bunch of water breathing potions.
I really like that.
Oh!
One more thing.
Any potion...
With...
Uh...
Redstone powder.
It's gonna make, um...
Duration increase.
I guess it's the best word to say that.
Maybe there's another word for it.
Okay.
There you go.
Look at this.
We already have all our knowledge built up.
From last season.
It's back.
Put these in here.
Maybe we should put the awkward ones there so we don't get confused.
Now, what else can we put in a potion?
I feel like there's gotta be new interactions with some of these.
Ah!
I know what it's gonna be, though.
Powered obsidian!
Let's try that!
Oh, it doesn't even go in.
Okay.
I could've sworn just any powder would work here, but...
Maybe not.
Put it back.
Actually, just throw these in here.
Look at this mechanism, if you haven't seen it yet.
Goes in like that.
They go through a complicated process downstairs and fly...
Into my hands.
Somehow that went through the window.
That's interesting.
But they plop...
They plop up here and fall through there and get crunched.
And then they come out like this into little powdery stones.
And it's amazing.
See that?
We even got one back.
Sometimes you get it back.
Efficiency.
What about copper nuggets?
I mean, if you can put stone in there, why not copper, right?
Nope.
Okay.
That don't work.
Let's try dirt.
I'm not sure if I ever tried that.
Okay.
Fine.
I feel like I should not be wearing the cardboard stuff.
I...
May have made a mistake just wearing this.
I mean, it's cool, but you're also really squishy.
Right?
I mean, I'm gonna die if I wear that.
Bad idea.
Fully armored.
Nice.
And then sometimes we'll use the...
I'm trying to think, when would be a good time to use cardboard?
Probably...
Oh!
I know where.
What about the skulk place?
Right?
Which I also want to find, by the way.
Still haven't found that.
Hmm.
That should maybe be my next big, uh, thing I do.
Actually, even before anything else.
Because finding skulk could maybe affect, uh, things and create, you know?
Maybe new discoveries there.
That's a big one.
Uh, let me see here.
Ferment...
Okay, let's just try this one at a time now.
Potion of poison.
Regeneration.
Fire resistance.
Healing.
Water breathing.
Infestation.
Uh, actually, let's do...
Fermentation.
Doesn't do anything.
Let's try the next.
Ah!
What's happening here?
Something's happening!
What's it gonna be?
I'm so excited for this.
There's no way...
This is not, uh...
I...
Okay.
I'm actually gonna cover the screen.
I'm covering the screen.
I can't see the color of the potion right now.
I think this is definitely not potion of weakness.
It's something else.
Potion of harming?
That's new!
It's gotta be.
I mean...
To be expected, I guess.
So you want to put that in a splash potion.
You want to splash that shit.
That's...
Wait, is that new?
Maybe I never discovered this.
This could be something really old.
Oh my god.
Am I...
Am I actually making crazy discoveries right now?
We need more ice.
Which means I need...
I need more sugar.
Which means I need, uh...
Cane.
I don't have it?
Frick!
Is there a way to get cane?
Dude, we should make another cane farm.
I made one, and it's not that hard to make.
Basically, you put an observer...
And you measure when the cane grows...
And as soon as it grows...
You use the, uh...
The slapper.
You know what I mean?
I feel like we should do that.
We, we...
I mean...
How else are we gonna make an infinite cake machine?
You gotta need sugar for that, right?
Sugar is important.
Oh, let's go feed the animals.
It's feeding time.
He's gonna multiply like crazy now.
Wow!
Bastard.
Uh, you wanna...
You wanna dance?
I can dance.
Actually, I don't need to hide.
I'm not afraid of you.
Oh, shit.
Come on.
Easy.
You come to my homestead?
You better not miss.
Okay, here we go.
There's so many!
Oh, my goodness.
We're doubling the numbers every time.
The growth is gonna be exponential.
And before you know it...
I will have food for infinity.
Okay, that's it.
I'm actually so happy I finally did this, uh...
Little enclosure there.
Pasture.
Makes everything so nice.
And you know what?
While I'm at it...
While I'm winning so much right now...
What's that doing there?
I am gonna...
Go find a carrot.
There's no way I don't have a carrot.
I just need one carrot.
How do I get carrots?
Wait.
I actually don't know how to get a carrot.
Maybe Stuart if he comes by.
But I don't see him.
Ah, man.
Just need one, and then I can multiply.
Um...
Okay, let's...
Let's, uh...
Yeah, I can't do this anymore, unfortunately.
Shit.
We're gonna come back to this.
To be, uh...
Continued.
Uh, you know...
I think I'm gonna keep these somewhere else.
Like here.
Yeah, I don't want these to get lost.
They're kind of important.
Gunpowder.
Really wish I could go flying right now, man!
I can't, though.
Not yet.
I need mending.
Uh, which reminds me...
Shall we try now again?
Maybe he has changed his mind.
Maybe he's been institutionalized.
Where did I leave the thing?
Outside, I think.
There it is.
Let's try and get mending now.
So that we can get flying.
And then with flying, we're gonna go find a carrot.
So that we can get a night vision potion.
So that we can comfortably go dig.
And find...
Uh, the skulk situation.
This is the order of events.
Let's see if this works.
Uh, let me try and push you into it.
I...
I know...
I'm a student, uh, counselor.
You...
I...
Or a career advisor.
You...
You wanna become a man that makes...
Mending.
Okay, I think you have to get out of the boat.
I don't...
I don't wanna have to do this, but...
Fine.
No, no.
What?
I knew it, man!
He's a butcher now.
Because of...
This, I guess.
Oh, you bastard.
There you go.
No more butchering...
Okay.
Brother.
You're pissing me off.
Don't touch my cookies.
In fact, I want you to take that cookie and put it somewhere.
Huh?
It worked!
Wow!
That's a good one already!
Dude, I'm actually gonna purchase that.
Uh, disconnect.
I'll take one of those.
I have money.
I don't know where from, but I have it.
Ah, wait a minute.
If I do this, he's gonna become experienced, and I can't change him.
Ooh, I can't...
I can't do this.
Oh, fuck.
I can't do it.
Oh, that pains me, dude!
Ah, shit.
Okay.
Let me just try again.
Okay, and then...
How did I make it work?
Maybe he needs to come from somewhere else and walk into it?
So, like, if I put this...
here...
And then I grab him?
Oh, wait.
Maybe it was completely...
Random.
Hmm.
Okay.
I have another idea.
We're gonna go back out here.
Maybe there was just something about that area we were in where he...
I don't know.
Couldn't do it before.
Maybe it's the portal.
Maybe he was afraid of the portal!
He was running away from it, right?
Let's go to the factory area.
Nice.
He does go across the tracks.
That's good.
Or does he?
Sir?
He does not.
Okay, fuck.
He does.
But it wasn't because I was jumping.
Okay, sir?
Check it out.
How did I make it work?
Is it because I jumped?
Maybe if I jump, it triggers him to...
somehow be closer to it?
I don't know what I'm saying.
Okay, he was going somewhere else.
He's still too close.
We gotta go even further.
Uh-oh.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You're not going anywhere.
God, I hate these guys so much.
They suck.
All right, you asked for it.
Come on.
Maybe I'll lock you...
Actually...
If his pathfinding is taking him over to one of the other workplaces, I'm gonna lock you inside.
That's what we're gonna do.
Maybe the pathfinding is gonna have problems then.
You bastard.
In fact, you're gonna get the same treatment as the zombie villager.
But since you're worth a little more to me, you're gonna...
You're gonna get to use spruce instead.
This is like the...
The virgin burke situation, while over here we have the chad spruce, you know?
Here you go.
Up, up, up, up.
We do need some room to...
No, we don't need any room for this guy.
Fuck him.
Fuck him, fuck
him.
So I can get in.
Now?
Suck on that.
Yeah!
Dude!
Tech discovered!
He doesn't even have a choice!
Wait, multi-shot.
This is so much better than what I did...
earlier.
Bookshelf.
Get out of here.
Dude, I broke the game.
Capac...
Wait, wait.
What the fuck is...
I...
Hmm, I don't know, actually.
Stop giving me the...
bookshelves, man.
Luck of the sea.
There it is, baby!
Thank God!
Wait, how does this...
Oh, right.
Yeah!
What a deal!
In fact, I'll take two.
Do I take three?
Oh, I can't.
Okay.
Need more money.
He's kind of...
That's kind of expensive, brother.
20...
of those?
Hmm.
Uh...
Listen, I know you did me a solid there, but...
I'm...
You're gonna have to stay in here for a little while longer, okay?
Maybe I'll give you some activities down here you can do.
You can play with this shulker box.
Look, it goes up and stuff.
See how it sort of does that?
That's fun, right?
Okay, see you tomorrow.
Goodbye.
Uh, wait a minute.
Uh, enemies can come in like this, so this is better.
Then again, hold on.
Spiders can come in too.
We gotta protect this guy.
This guy needs protection.
Let's just make a proper roof for him.
Or bring him over to my house.
Maybe I actually put him in my basement down here.
I forgot how to actually get down.
There's like a secret switch-sharu combo somewhere.
Like a combination you have to press.
Was it that one?
Was not that one.
Hmm.
I actually forgot how to do this.
Uh, wait.
What was the trick?
How do I get down?
Aha!
Oh!
Okay, there's an issue with this.
Don't worry about it.
We're gonna fix it later.
We're gonna just create a...
We're gonna create an issue on GitHub for that.
And then hope someone comes in and does it.
Lead!
Don't need it anymore.
Where do I put that?
I guess equipment.
It's an equipment.
Wait.
I think it's...
Is it already farming time again?
Or feeding?
Let's do one more round.
Let's go to sleep and then do it.
Oh yeah.
There's gonna be so many here.
Hey, everybody!
Oh wait, they haven't grown yet.
The kids haven't grown, but that's okay.
You can still feed the parents.
Honey!
I fed the parents!
Long awaited, uh...
Sequel.
There you go.
Dude, the slaughtering is gonna be biblical.
When we finally do it.
Hoo-hoo!
That's gonna be a lot.
Nice.
Um...
Yeah, unfortunately no carrots.
We gotta go find that.
But to find that, we need the flying.
And to find flying, we need mending.
Which we have now!
Yoink!
Watch this!
Mending!
Hey-hey!
There we go!
And we're back in business, dude.
We're gonna fly now.
That is so nice.
Let's go flying!
We also need to repair it first.
So I guess we just gotta get experience.
Um...
I think this one has a lot of hidden experience right now.
But I'm a little...
scared.
So I'm just gonna dig a hole.
That's the way I do when I get scared.
Then I grab the lava.
Like that, and then we destroy it.
Wait, what?
There's nothing?
Huh.
I could've sworn that was gonna be experience in there.
But okay.
Fine.
Put it back.
That's cool.
Um...
Experience, experience.
I guess I just kill some things, or go mine.
I actually forgot how to...
How do I actually...
The way mending works is that whenever I get experience, it's actually stealing the experience.
That's right.
That's how that works.
So it's stealing the experience from me, but it's using it to repair.
So it's like a trade-off.
I basically just gotta go kill some things.
Oh, I forgot to protect that guy over there.
That's why we came back.
Do that now.
Make a tiny roof for him.
Wait, I wonder if they can open doors.
No, they can open doors, right?
Yeah, yeah, they can open doors.
Oh my god, I don't even have enough.
That's crazy.
Gonna be a terribly looking little home for him here.
Not the virgin birch.
I'm sorry, I promised never to give you the birch, but here we are.
You can have a light.
There you go.
Enjoy.
And I guess I'll leave you a little air hole somewhere.
There you go.
That's an air hole.
You can also see the stars.
Never mind, there's a tree.
Enjoy.
Okay, so mending is done.
Dude, can we put mending on the bow?
Maybe...
I actually don't know.
Can you put mending on a bow?
Maybe you can't.
Either that, or it's incompatible with some of the other stuff that's on the bow right now.
There's two explanations there.
But, uh, I do want to just keep the mending as well.
In case we need to, you know, put it on another, uh, thing.
Okay.
Only level 13, which is kind of sad.
Very sad, in fact.
We just need one arrow, too.
Money back in.
Now we can go flying.
Should we go find some carrots?
Yeah, oh, the compass!
Right!
Uh, let me see this now.
What was it?
I'll know it when I see it.
Compass, compass, compass.
Oh, maybe it's actually at the end.
Or...
Nether?
Use a compass on a lodestone.
I actually can't believe why I can't do this.
Never mind.
I do know why I can't do it.
Here's the explanation.
To make a lodestone, I'm pretty sure I need netherite.
And I don't have it.
Because I always died before I got home with it.
That's why I don't have this.
So we gotta go to the nether again.
Speaking of the nether, what actually did happen to my digging machine?
Is it just gone?
This says minecart with furnace.
But is it really a minecart with a furnace?
You know what I mean?
Or is it something else?
Didn't I have a contraption on wheels?
Maybe it did get destroyed, man.
But how?
Wait.
So I was digging...
I was digging in the nether.
And I ran out of...
Wait, maybe the digging machine is still down there.
So I was digging.
And I got a little greedy.
I had low HP.
I somehow died.
Maybe it was lava, actually.
I died from lava, I think.
I couldn't find my stuff again.
I think the digging machine is down there.
Dude, we should go back down there and find it.
I think it's down there!
The whole ass digging machine with, like, 9,000 drillers is in the nether right now.
And I think I remember where, too, actually.
So we're not gonna need the elytra right now.
Keep it there.
Which means we keep this here.
Do I not have anything other golden?
I don't want to be using a chest plate made of gold.
That's too much.
In my opinion.
Let's do a helmet.
Like that.
That way we have more protection.
And we're safer, too.
Oh!
Oy!
We are gonna bring...
Ah!
Damn it!
Gosh!
Dang it!
I was about to say, let's bring night vision.
But I don't have carrots.
And I needed to find carrots with my...
thingy...
first.
Ah...
Okay.
We have a long list of things to do right now.
Let's do it.
Let's not cry about it like a little girl.
We are gonna just get to work.
Although I used to cry a lot as a 9-year-old girl.
Put this here.
Three water bottles.
And then put this there.
And then...
It's gonna become awkward!
We're gonna make it into magma.
And then we add the redstone.
Because we also want fire protection when we're in the nether.
Come on.
Oh, no.
Keep it there.
There you go.
Anything else it should bring?
What was this?
I'm infested.
Oh, wait.
Is it...
These are the little assholes.
Are they gonna pop out of me?
Are they inside my bloodstream right now?
Causing a ruckus.
I'm not...
Oh, I'll wait.
I'll wait.
We'll see what happens.
I mean, I have to wait for this potion anyway.
Put this in there.
Boop.
There we go.
Three potions of fire resistance.
It's wonderful.
Do I need to bring night vision?
I think I do, man.
We gotta go find a carrot.
Let's just go find it.
Right now.
Don't overthink it.
In fact, I think I may know where to find it.
Usually you find this stuff in villages, right?
Because they be harvesting carrots and stuff.
So let's go to the village I was just at.
Whee!
Keep an eye on durability, of course.
Oh my god, that's actually going down pretty...
Wait, is it?
Dude, we may need the other enchant as well to make it last longer.
I actually didn't think about that.
Oh, since I'm here...
Maybe we do a bit of...
Killing.
A bit of murder in the morning.
Tell me you have carrots.
You got taters?
Oh, that's where I've already been.
A part of me thinks I should pick up all these mushrooms here, but I don't want to.
Oh, I needed this, didn't I?
Sugar for me.
I've been there already.
I think this is a dead end.
There's nothing here.
Unless you sell me carrots.
Oh, oh, you want carrots.
Oh, bastard.
So close, though.
What was that?
Oh, that's the fox.
Carrots?
Is that carrot?
No.
I...
No, that's...
Okay.
That's haters?
Yeah.
Man, they have everything but carrots.
I think I'm in the wrong biome.
I gotta find a village in a different biome for them to have carrots.
What the hell was that?
Sounded like a pig getting murdered.
I just had a genius idea.
This is how I'm gonna remember how to make Potion of Weakness.
We're gonna go find an igloo.
That's how I learned it the first place, remember?
At least I'm like 90% sure.
They had a whole setup in there.
You heard me.
A whole setup in there.
Okay, I don't think they have anything I need here.
Unfortunately.
Oh!
Whoa!
Pay...
I mean, I'll take that.
And some...
Yeah, okay, why not?
Thanks.
I say cash was just stealing it.
I'm so evil.
Why am I like this?
Wait, hold on.
Calculating.
Okay, I got it.
Back we go.
Oh!
Uh...
I need unbreaking.
On this.
This is what I need.
Otherwise, I'm gonna have to repair it constantly, man.
Look how fast it's going down.
Like, that's not normal.
I need durability.
Yeah, this trip took like a quarter of that whole durability bar.
That's...
That's unacceptable.
So, let's see if we can actually...
Can we...
I wonder if we can get that...
Right now.
I think we're too low level.
Whoa!
Power 4!
That's kind of a nuts enchantment.
Okay.
I mean, I'm still too low level though, but...
You know.
No more flying.
Until we have this issue fixed.
Man, I thought we were done after mending.
And then I remember that.
Terrible.
I needed sugar to make, uh...
Oh!
I remember.
Fermented ice.
Uh...
So, we gotta go here.
No, sugar.
Up, up, up, up, up, up.
Wait, wait, wait.
Sugar cane.
Can we crush it?
Maybe.
Ah!
Dude, we gotta...
Always crush it when you can.
Here we go.
I love when it crushes.
You know what I mean?
Okay.
That's definitely twice the amount of what I've gotten normally, so that's fantastic.
And then we need ice.
Which are over here.
Sugar.
Wait, how does this work?
God damn it.
Ah!
Mushroom.
Right.
Good thing I brought one home.
Okay, so we tried one potion.
Let's try the others.
It's not an empty one for sure.
Maybe it's fire resistance.
No, I don't think it's fire resistance, actually.
Nope.
Water breathing.
Last one I tried was potion of healing.
Poison?
Oh!
Ooh!
This could be weakness.
Poison is like...
When you're poisoned, you become weak, right?
It's like being sick.
Here we go!
What's gonna happen?
I think we got it.
This has to be it.
Ah!
Wait, we tried that already!
Fuck!
Ah!
That's a...
Blunder!
Wait, I need to write this down.
Uh...
Oh, God.
What did I do, even?
What did I just do?
What did I put in?
I forgot what I put in?
I can't write it down.
It's gonna be unsure.
Shit.
Oh, crap.
I can't believe I've done this.
I'm gonna need more spider eyes.
Of course, I don't have any.
I gotta go kill spiders.
Oh, man.
This is like the worst turn of events right now.
I can't believe it.
Mushrooms.
No, that's...
Greenery.
Actually, that's farming.
What are these doing here?
Uno Torcho.
Coppices.
Am I ready?
Should I just go to the nether?
Do I need anything else?
We have a crazy pickaxe now.
We have a bow.
We have arrow.
We have pretty much everything we need.
I don't like E-exotic.
Get rid of that.
Perhaps I'll take some...
gold.
And give it to the pigs.
That's one thing I'll do.
And some potions of fire resistance.
Oh, right.
But I needed carrots.
So in order to get carrots, we gotta...
fly.
But we can't fly.
Because we don't have unbreaking.
And we can't get unbreaking because we don't have a level.
So we gotta go to the nether.
Ah, but I can't go to the nether because I don't have night vision.
But to get night vision, we need carrots.
There's a problem here.
Let's just...
You know what?
Let's just go feed the animals.
Seems like the better option right now.
I feel like I'm kind of stuck here.
And it's not even my fault.
Oh my god!
There's so many!
Look at this shit!
Holy crap!
At some point, killing these things is gonna be a nuisance.
So we need an automated killer.
Holy crap!
Here you go!
Eat it up, brothers and sisters!
Eat, eat, eat, eat, eat, eat, eat, eat, eat, eat.
Everyone gets to eat.
Wait, why am I getting experience?
Wait, what's happening here?
Why am I getting experience?
What the fuck?
Huh?
Wait, why?
What's happening?
I am so confused right now.
I'm picking up experience.
Like, feeding them gives experience somehow.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay.
You motherfucker.
You asked for it.
I have no idea how that just gave me experience.
But that's okay.
Put that in there.
Gonna take some of this.
Yeah.
Okay, I think we're ready.
Put that there.
I'm just gonna go to the nether.
Fuck it.
We don't need night vision.
I'm just gonna say no to the night vision.
I do want fire resistance.
Yeah, I'm happy with that.
Let's go find this digging machine.
Can't be too hard to find.
And I'm pretty sure I dug holes back here.
I actually know the exact spot.
I just need to look around.
I was in despair last time, you know?
Because I had lost all my items and it was a big deal.
But this time I have the mental fortitude of a titan.
Oh, over there.
I was on the wrong path.
I'm actually just gonna eat this now.
Oh,
I could have maybe brought my flyer just to, you know, for stuff like this.
For situations like this, it's kinda nice.
It's a little...
Oh, wait.
Maybe I didn't jump down.
Maybe I...
Was it back here I dug?
I dug here, didn't I?
How am I actually this good?
Wait, this...
Unless this is the old way I dug and I disbanded this idea.
Oh, God, I'm hitting my head.
Oh, this is horrible.
Yeah, I...
This was not the path.
I need to sort of align like...
Oh, no, no, I'm hitting my head again.
Okay, if you don't look, it doesn't hurt.
Survival tips for prison.
I must have jumped down.
That's what I did.
Oh, God.
What's up, brother man?
Oh.
Hello.
Oh, okay.
You're a feisty one.
I'm just gonna jump, man.
Am I?
Am I gonna...
Why does it...
I feel like I'm gonna die if I jump.
Well, did I go back here?
No, I'm like 90% sure I jumped.
I'm just gonna jump.
Will I be able to handle it mentally if I die?
Answer's no.
Oh, I see where I can survive.
Oh, my God.
There's no way I jumped back there last time.
I would have died.
Let me eat my...
Oh.
Oh, you know what I should do?
Ah, I don't have my flyer with me.
Why am I forgetting the name?
I could have had it on me while I do this to get experience for it.
But, you know, getting experience on my body is not bad either.
I do like that.
Well, I think I ducked somewhere around here.
I see a torch.
I think it's, like...
We're close.
And we have a fantastic pickaxe with us, too.
Oh, I see it.
I saw it.
Right here.
Entrance...
Found.
Eat...
Meat.
Sit...
Sit down.
Listen to the sound.
Because this music slaps.
Okay.
We are going to go systematically around now.
So, we just came down.
We're going left.
We're going to see what's in here.
And we're going to find this machine.
Because I think it's down here.
Waiting.
Patiently.
And pretty soon, the machine shall dig again.
And you know what?
Maybe I should be putting torches.
If I had put torches last time I was here, I could have survived.
That was a major blunder.
Wait.
Hmm.
Okay, so we came here.
We're going to go this way first.
Let's see where we end up.
Oh, did I?
Ah, okay.
I'm actually going to cover that up.
So, everywhere there's torches, we have been.
And we should not go back to that place.
Except, I did put torches somewhere in the past.
Around these parts.
So, it doesn't, you know, hold 100% of the time.
This one's also clean, I think.
Now we go back.
We should arrive back where we started.
At the, uh...
Staircase.
Then we go down one more level.
Maybe I'm actually wrong.
Maybe the machine isn't here.
Could the machine have gone bad, somehow?
Like...
I don't know.
Guys.
Do you think the machine is here?
Yes, or...
Wait, how am I lost already?
Fuck, I missed it.
Is the machine here?
Yes, or no?
I'm gonna say yes.
It's down here.
The machine is here.
I will find...
Ooh, okay.
We're friends.
Here we go.
Staircase.
Okay.
Go further down.
Let's go left first.
Wait, what?
Wait, how does this work?
This doesn't...
Ah, okay, okay.
Left first.
So, we're just gonna keep going this way.
Gonna be a lot of searching and looking.
As soon as we find a really big open area, that's when we know.
Okay, this way now?
Now we're actually walking below the stairs.
Keep putting torches.
So, this is the path I was on just now.
These are the stairs, I think?
Yep.
Nice.
We're gonna keep going this way now.
Nothing there.
I actually feel pretty confident.
I feel good about this whole situation.
Okay.
Another area checked off the list.
Now we're back here.
This one.
I already put torches here.
I have a feeling this is the first place I dug when I came down here initially.
Because I started putting torches and then I ran out of torches.
And I couldn't do that anymore.
And here I hit this disgusting material, so I decided to turn around.
Understandable, of course.
Nobody likes gravel.
Or appendages.
Did I just pass by the staircase?
God damn it.
I thought I saw something.
Maybe I didn't see something.
Wait, where am I?
Whoa.
I'm like super lost.
Ah, wait.
I only made one path here.
So this...
Ah, this is the staircase.
Good.
Now we go this way.
We're gonna have torches on the right side, not left.
The universal rule of Minecraft shall not be broken today.
Do I dare?
I dare.
This is not me breaking the universal rules of Minecraft right now.
If you think about it, these are actually on the right side right now.
If I do this.
Right?
I just happen to be coming from the other side, so it doesn't matter.
Oh my god, this is like...
I somehow made this into a maze.
Like, it's so successful at confusing me.
Wait, what?
Oh, this is the staircase.
Uh, further down I guess.
Maybe here?
I'm just confused how I'm not finding this big ass place I dug.
I dug like 10,000 football fields worth of netherite here.
I mean netherrack.
This could be it, actually.
Another thing we could do is try and listen for enemies.
Because I'm pretty sure I did not have torches when I was doing that.
Which means it's a big open area.
With lots of room for mobs to spawn in.
With no light, right?
So we should pay attention to that.
Another dead end here.
I wouldn't be surprised if what I did was I suddenly started digging in a random-ass direction.
Like, up or down, and then just continued on in a random path, you know?
Which is obviously not good for me right now.
Okay, so...
This is like the bottom, though.
Fuck, how did I...
This is not boating well.
Adrian is rolling in his grave right now.
Oh god, this is gonna be...
I feel...
I've gone through everything.
Okay, here's the...
I'm just gonna go with my gut.
I'm gonna close my eyes.
I'm gonna count to four.
I actually went above four.
But I'm actually gonna just...
You know how you just sort of go?
It's down here.
I can smell it.
Let's just try and...
Put ourselves in the situation of past me.
What would I have done?
I would have gone this way.
And then I would have gone right like this.
And then...
Then...
Then I would have...
I would have dug...
Somewhere.
Non-obvious.
So it wasn't there.
Dude, what if...
You remember one of these paths I covered up with netherrack?
Imagine that's one of the paths I took.
That would be insane.
There's no way that's the case, right?
So we just did that.
Huh.
How on earth...
Like...
This is really impressive.
How did I manage to hide this place?
Every single weird path we find out, we're gonna take.
We're no longer just gonna run back and forth.
We take the weird paths.
We're gonna be no one and we're gonna go nowhere.
Cold water music.
Now, digging doesn't make sense.
Because, you know, that doesn't make sense.
There's no other thing else to add to that, really.
But it's not this one.
I did pass by some non-obvious paths earlier.
Question is, where did that happen?
Maybe it's, like, down here.
I'm actually gonna take this.
My brother needs experience, you know?
Another thing I can do is just start digging randomly and hopefully hit upon...
Um...
The big open space.
That's another option, actually.
That's the nuclear option.
I may have to, uh, do that.
But we'll see if I can...
Manage to find it first without doing that.
See, this right here looks kind of promising.
You know?
This is the stuff of dreams.
That is the stuff of dreams right there.
And you'll see why in a second.
This right here is so dreamy.
I'm feeling this.
I think we are on the right path.
Okay, that's the bottom.
I'm just gonna...
I'm just gonna do a little digging.
Just a little bit.
Just gonna see what's...
What's down here.
Okay.
I think we were a little...
We were definitely higher than the bottom, right?
I think we're too low.
That's the problem.
And add to that, that I've been cold since 81.
So, based on that...
Maybe here?
Okay, so we're back...
Oh my god.
How is this possible?
Okay.
New plan.
It's a good one.
We're gonna go all the way to the first one up here.
That one.
And then we're gonna take the unorthodox paths now.
Because in the beginning, I just ran back and forth, right?
Could I have been such a demon that I actually closed off the path I took behind me?
When I went?
I almost refused to believe that.
I don't think I wanna imagine what those levels of demon are.
But that's just not something I would like to think about right now.
That means nuclear option is looking better and better as time goes on here.
Like, imagine I found lava and I closed it off, right?
And now I can never find it.
This looked promising, briefly.
Where the fuck?
Is it?
Did I...
What did I do?
How is this possible?
I'm, like, 100% sure that nobody knows where this is.
Not just me, you know?
Like, nobody knows.
And if that somebody knows, they're actually a god.
Like, your brain needs to be studied.
Not good.
No likey that.
Is it time for nuclear?
I think we go nuclear now.
And the way we're gonna do...
We're gonna take samples.
I'll show you what I mean.
So we're gonna go as high as we can here.
Okay.
We're gonna go a little in this direction.
Like this.
Now we just dig down.
Because at some point we're gonna hit a big open area.
We're gonna do it carefully, of course, so we don't hit lava or some bullshit like that.
Okay, that's the...
That's a bad sample.
Now we know.
What you don't know of doesn't hurt.
Don't look at it.
Let's take a sample over here.
Back at the staircase.
We go a little bit this way now.
Sample time.
Hello?
What is...
Oh.
Intriguing.
Could just be one of the random paths.
That I made.
Okay, that's the bottom.
Bad sample.
Now, of course, this is assuming it's all nearby here.
But I think it is.
Back to the staircase.
Now we go a little further down like this.
Let's do a random sample here.
Like, I'm gonna find this.
Mark my words.
Shit.
Oh, hey, we're getting experience.
Silver lining.
I'm gonna...
You know what?
In order to find a place born of chaos, I think we need to be chaotic.
We shouldn't think.
We should just feel.
I'm just gonna go, man.
Okay.
Bad, bad sample.
Let's try...
I'm gonna go a little further and just...
Go on field.
Right here.
Was I even down here?
I'm trying to think.
Yeah, yeah, I was down here.
I was down here.
For a second, I was like...
When I decided to go do the big dig, you know?
Was I even...
in this spot?
I think I was, though.
Shit!
I mean...
We...
Oh...
We can't have been close to the bottom, right?
When we did the dig.
That doesn't make any sense.
Staircase.
I think it was further up.
It's like one of the only explanations here.
Did I go even further?
I think we should just keep taking samples here, but further down each line.
So I took one here, and it wasn't good.
We're gonna go further and take another sample.
And we're gonna take it this way now.
Right here.
It's a good sample.
Oh!
Oh my god!
I thought it...
for a second!
You're teasing me!
Oh!
You know what I need?
I need that tech that they have on...
that they use in...
or they use in the Egypt.
On the pyramids.
You know how they detect...
open areas...
inside the pyramid?
I need that.
I need to send in sound waves and see how they bounce around.
To find out, uh...
what comes back and then analyze it, you know?
And figure out if there's any open space somewhere here.
It's not here.
This is the staircase again.
So I took the sample here last time.
Let's go a little further and do a sample back here instead.
Oh, I did do a sample there already.
Let's try this direction.
Who knows?
Okay.
I mean, we're super close to the bottom all the time.
Level 22!
We're getting somewhere with the experience at least.
And I'm actually gonna use this for my netherrack.
Like, made for it.
And this.
So smart.
Okay, I have a better idea.
Let's just, uh...
do this more systematically now.
I feel like chaos is not the answer to chaos.
What we can do...
It... oh.
Wait, what?
Am I confusing myself with my own dig right now?
The one I just did?
Where's the staircase?
Oh, shit.
Brother...
Show me what's good.
I'm actually kind of lost now.
Like, I can't even...
climb my way around.
That's the bottom.
Hmm.
This is lava.
Let's try this one.
No, I don't feel it.
What's this?
Oh my god, I'm going in circles.
This way.
Okay, I have a better idea.
How about...
Um...
Wait, is this the stair...
This is not the staircase.
Never mind.
Staircase is...
here.
Okay, check it out.
What we're gonna do...
We're gonna go all the way to the top now.
And I'm gonna take samples at specific points.
And just go down in the staircase.
That's it.
That way we penetrate all layers and...
If I happen to have been below one of them, I will not make that mistake again.
So this is where we entered.
Let's go a little this way.
And just go down.
This whole area shall be analyzed now.
Okay, we're...
We're hitting these again.
That's okay.
We're gonna keep going down.
The old tunnels are dead dead now.
They're dead to me.
This is the new thing.
I don't have a peek though.
Keep going.
Okay, so this is a bad one.
Now, it is possible, of course, that I started all this way further in this direction.
That there's no way I could have hit it from this angle.
Don't look at it.
Oh my god.
At this point, I almost want to make another digging machine to find my old digging machine.
And then combine them to create an ultra-powered digging machine.
Let's do a hole here.
This is getting ridiculous.
Oh my god.
Wait, why did that hurt?
It didn't hurt when I walk on it normally.
So why'd it hurt now?
I'm confused.
Ah, wait.
Is it because I had fire protection?
I could actually...
Wait a second.
No, okay.
For a second there, I thought something was going on.
I'm actually gonna drink one of these.
Littering.
Yeah, now I don't take damage.
It makes so much sense, too.
Man, this is insane.
Wow.
How the fuck?
How actually is this so hidden?
What the hell did I do when I was here?
How is this possible?
Where did I go?
It's a fucking mystery.
This is a more guarded secret than the shit they have at Area 51, man.
It's blowing my mind.
I'm okay, though.
We're gonna find it.
It's actually not a big deal.
Well, we're gonna find it.
You freaking bastard trying to interrupt my search.
And you as well.
Get out of here.
Okay.
The problem is I can't even go in my old footsteps now because I kind of messed up the entire place now.
You know, it's...
I somehow...
You know what this is?
This is like me walking into a crime scene leaving my DNA everywhere.
Just rubbing my face and my cheek up against all the evidence.
You know, and...
Lying on the floor kicking everything and screaming.
And now I don't know what the fuck happened in this place.
This is the equivalent.
This is what happened.
Shit!
I'm gonna go this way.
I should have...
I should have left the crime scene undisturbed.
And just paid more attention.
So now we went quite far.
I feel like digging.
And it's not even because I don't know where this place is right now that I'm looking for.
It's because I just...
I like digging.
Shit!
Okay, we're very close to the bottom now so I think we're too low.
Okay, check it out.
I have another idea.
We're just gonna go...
We're just gonna do this.
Hey, you know what?
Let's work backwards.
If I came down here with a big-ass digging machine, one that is super wide, think of something that is incredibly big and weighs a lot, right?
And I'm not talking about your mom.
But I have this digging machine.
It's massive.
I would need to go to a place that is already quite massive before I start digging.
So what do I need to look for?
Anything that isn't a tunnel.
Right?
I need to find an open area.
Well, obviously I've been looking for that, but...
The beginnings of an open area, you know?
Like, anything that smells like the start of an open area.
That's what we need to do.
Where would I have gone?
If I had a great big digging machine, what would be my first destination down here?
I would probably have thought, let me go up a bit, you know?
So that I don't fall into lava or something.
But I'm actually just gonna dig.
Because I like digging.
Oh!
It's okay.
Look down before you walk.
Get away from me.
MLG reactions.
Brother, what?
Okay.
I hate this path.
Try the other way.
You know, at this point, the crime scene is so messed up anyway, I'm just gonna keep doing it.
I'm gonna keep rubbing my cheek on everything.
In fact, I'm gonna probably spit in a corner and take a leak on the evidence.
Like, whatever.
You know?
It's already fucked.
There's no reason to have any decency anymore.
How do I get myself into this shit all the time?
Like, I feel like it's constantly, you know?
Why am I always in these situations?
It doesn't make any sense.
I feel like I'm unlucky.
Did I get that?
I did get it.
Okay.
Okay, try this way now.
Shit!
Oh!
We're okay.
I keep thinking my...
Like, we're gonna fall into lava and die, but we have lava protection, so it's actually no problem.
But then again, we could fall down and die from a great height.
There's always something to be afraid of.
Okay, I'm feeling this way now.
I'm just gonna start digging like crazy.
Like, I don't give a shit.
We're gonna find it.
This is the way.
It'll happen.
Okay.
Go back.
How is this so hidden?
It is...
It's like when you lose your phone, you know?
Or your car keys.
Except I don't have car keys, but I have keys, you know?
And you just had them in your hand, and they freaking disappear off the face of the earth.
Like, they fell into the back rooms.
There's no other explanation for how they could have just disappeared like that.
That's how I feel.
Not about some little car keys, but about 10,000 fucking football fields worth of area.
How can I misplace that?
How is it so lost?
I don't understand.
It doesn't make sense.
I'm okay, though.
Like, it's actually fine.
Okay, so we're back here now.
Let's go higher up.
All right.
Run it back from the top.
We're going this way.
Shit, man.
I feel like the guy that pushes a rock up a mountain, you know what I mean?
Forget his name, but it's like terrible times for him.
Okay, I hear a bunch of lava here.
There's no way I would have dug there.
Show me!
Show me the football field!
Put me in the game, coach!
Oh my god, what?
It's not here.
Okay, wait, wait, wait.
No.
Keep digging.
You know what?
I'm not even trying to find this place, actually.
Yeah, I'm just...
I'm finding netherite right now.
That's what I'm doing.
As soon as I stop looking for it, it'll fall into my lap.
You'll see.
That's horrible.
Oh!
Drink this!
I'm not afraid of you.
Okay, I don't want to go that way.
Not because I'm not afraid, because I hate it.
It's just not a good time that way.
Oh, man.
Dear God!
Show me the way!
I think I'm actually fucking going nuts here.
Where is it?
Fucking lava.
Like, I don't understand how it can disappear.
It doesn't make any sense.
It's like a cruel joke.
What's that?
Wait a minute.
There's no torches here.
Hello?
Did we find it?
This is it!
Oh, my God.
We found it.
Now the question is, is it here?
Holy shit, dude.
I can't believe it.
Wow.
And the funny thing is, I don't even know how we got here.
I have no idea where I am.
How do we get here?
It makes no sense.
I'm gonna get experience while I'm here.
I'm not coming home empty-handed.
Tell me the thing is here.
I think we got it, dude!
But why is it so small?
Didn't I make a, like, a massive one?
What the hell is this?
There's items here?
Wait!
Did
they just disappear?
Wait, what?
I thought I was gonna die.
Dude, I...
I came late.
I had the items that were right here.
Oh, my God.
If I had been a little faster.
Also, I'm, like, so sure I had a massive digging machine.
Like, did I only have a 3x3?
Could've sworn I had a...
My memories are getting mixed up here.
I don't understand.
Anyway, uh...
Diorite.
Wait, did I make a digging machine after this?
Wait a sec.
I am so confused.
Oh, my God.
I could've had my netherite!
No!
Man!
Oh, imagine I came earlier.
I mean, normally, you don't wanna do that earlier, but in this case, I would love to do that earlier.
Shit.
Wait, it's time I shit?
No, that's the thing I just dropped.
Okay.
Uh...
Dude, we're gonna bring this with us.
Wait, uh, how does this work again?
Oh, wait, fuck, I can't even...
Oh, no.
We can't even pick it up.
We need...
We need a switch.
Wait, hold on.
Redstone?
Blackstone?
Oh?
Oh.
Going for a ride, huh?
Uh...
A button!
We can make a button!
Blackstone!
Dude, I'm a genius.
Wait, what?
I guess we polish it!
Now, get...
Oh, no, how do I get you out?
I guess I...
Do that.
Now, piss off.
Go away.
My machine.
I gotta be fast!
Shit!
Oh, my God!
I hate that mechanic so much!
It's so stupid!
Wait, how does this work?
I don't understand.
No!
Huh?
Wait.
Wait a minute.
Uh...
Maybe we need a more permanent sort of...
Let's make this!
I'm a genius.
Look.
Did I make it?
Now, grab it.
Incredible!
Wow!
Next level tech happening here.
Get rid of that crap.
The gym actually saves the day.
Can you believe that?
Dude, I knew the minecart with the furnace wasn't really a minecart with the furnace.
I knew it from the start.
Okay, so, guys, we're not...
We're actually just gonna keep digging.
I'm here!
We're gonna keep digging.
Fuck it!
Time to dig!
That's right!
Uh...
How many rails do I even have?
It's gonna be a little...
Oh, actually, maybe I should grab my pressure plate.
It's gonna come in handy.
Yeah, give me that.
I don't want this, though.
Pressure plate good.
Button bad.
Oh, wait.
We actually kind of need to...
Lock rotation.
Oh, wait.
I can't move it and stand on it.
Wait.
I need another solution.
Damn, I don't have that.
Lever is...
Wait!
Oh, man.
Can I not make it out of anything else?
Wait, do I even have wood?
This is crazy.
Okay, whatever.
Oh!
Lava.
Wait, maybe I already tried to dig here and it failed.
That's why I didn't do this.
Bye-bye.
What happened there?
He just...
He was like Terminator, we know, with his height...
With his thumbs up.
Going down the lava.
See ya.
I guess you're...
Okay.
Good luck.
Okay, that's a bad way to go.
We don't want to go that way.
Let's dig in this direction.
In fact, I'm gonna go grab this...
rail here.
This direction now.
Okay.
And then, and then, when we're done here, we're gonna find our way out of here and we're gonna forever make it easy to come back.
Because, hot damn, this was...
a pain to find.
Wow.
Lock that, rotation.
Wonderful.
Is it going on its own, though?
It needed power, right?
I don't actually know if I have coal in there.
I don't think I have coal.
Wait, unless this machine predates the coal?
Oh my god!
Guys, this predates the coal era.
So that means my big-ass wide mama machine came later.
But when did she come?
When did that happen?
Where did I use it?
Did I lose it?
Maybe I lost it in some kind of explosion later on.
Oh my god.
What the fuck?
I was like, this is not even a furnace machine!
Oh, there's lava right above it.
Oh!
This is getting a little risky.
Here you go, sir.
You can have more.
Wait, is that you?
It's you.
Okay, faster!
Wait a minute, did I come back to the nether with the big-ass digging machine?
Wait a minute.
No way.
No, no, no.
Absolutely not.
You know what?
I'm gonna take this and throw it away.
because I'm a hater.
There's too much of this.
I only want the good stuff.
In fact, I'm gonna...
Oh, no.
Oh, no!
No!
Fuck me!
I knew there was lava up there.
That was a mistake.
Okay, thank god the machine survived.
Whew!
For a second I ever thought all was lost.
You're the one.
Go faster.
There's...
We're leaving.
Nope.
No thanks.
I'm good.
We're gonna dig in somewhere completely different direction here, because I hate lava.
This is what happens when you don't have your keybinds in order!
I'm gonna die!
Actually, I'm okay!
Whoa!
I took no damage at all!
I thought I was dying, man!
Oh!
Nope, nope, nope, nope, nope.
Keybinds are in order now.
You cannot fuck with me.
Holy crap!
Let's dig this way now.
I have a good feeling about this dig.
Okay, now.
This.
That one.
Stand on it.
Lock it.
Like that.
Push.
Start digging.
There's fucking lava again!
Wait, why does this suck so much right now?
This place used to rock, and now it sucks!
What is actually going on?
Oh my god.
You know what?
I'm gonna leave this here.
It's light.
This is absolutely horrendous.
Eat the meat.
I used to dig for miles and miles here, and now all of a sudden I can't go ten centimeters without having a catastrophe happen?
Doesn't make any sense.
Okay.
We're gonna dig...
Um...
I am not leaving this place until I have at least ten netherites in my back pocket.
This way now.
What?
Hold on.
What the hell happened to my assembler?
Dude, don't tell me that got...
Wait a minute.
Maybe it's already active, actually.
Are you working?
Oh!
Oh my god!
Hallelujah!
What the heck, man?
Wow!
Hey, you hungry?
Here you go.
Eat.
Well, you weren't that hungry, but...
I gotcha.
Keep digging.
Dig, dig, dig, dig, dig, dig, dig, dig.
We're back in business.
We found a good spot here.
Oh, yeah!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Uh-oh.
As soon as it lights up, you know it's lava.
Oh.
Motherfucker.
It's actually kind of cool that you have, um...
There's a safe space when you're on the tracks, you know?
Do I just keep going here?
I...
I think I just keep going.
I feel good.
I feel really good, actually.
Just be ready to grab it if shit goes south.
Wait, what happened?
What's wrong with you?
Did I put it too far forwards?
I think I may have...
Oh, I actually...
No, I think it ran out of tracks.
That's what happened.
No, it did not run out of tracks.
Tracks.
Interesting.
Alright, well...
We're digging.
Actually, we're super safe.
I should just stand, like, linearly here, you know?
If lava comes, I just stand on the tracks, like, immediately.
There's no reason to panic at all.
This is how safe everything is.
Oh, crap.
Uh-oh.
Wait a minute.
We don't even need tracks.
We can actually go without tracks.
If you think about it.
Are you thinking about it?
Now think about what it would have been like if you were born blind.
And add that to your analysis.
Only five torches left.
Faster.
It's digging a long time.
Does that mean it's collecting the good stuff?
Oh, give me that.
I mean, if it starts digging for a long time, we know it's a good sign, right?
The good stuff is coming.
Faster.
Dig for me.
Oh, here we go.
Lava.
Don't panic.
Stand on the tracks.
Just like we practiced.
And everything went well?
That's how you handle that situation.
In fact, whenever you panic, you actually...
It's not good to panic.
You know what I mean?
Just don't panic.
It's much easier.
Oh, no.
Uh.
I think I went a little too far there.
Do that.
Go.
From now on, we will never panic again.
Everything's under control.
Because this is the way you should do it.
Keep moving.
Part of me wants to come back with the furnace, but...
We gotta have at least one netherite.
One.
Just one.
Wait a minute.
Are we traversing into a shitty biome?
This doesn't look good.
Maybe.
It's not digging.
Why are you not digging?
You have plenty of tracks.
Hello?
Oh.
I see.
That's what happened.
Faster.
I think we're entering a new biome here.
And I actually don't like it.
So I'm gonna...
I'm gonna go somewhere else.
This is bad.
Let's do this instead.
We're gonna go like this.
A little more.
Make some space.
That's a nice shovel I got here.
Wow.
Beautiful.
Dude, I can't believe we don't even need the assembly mechanism.
Oh my god.
Oh, wait.
I misplaced it.
Shit.
No!
It's over.
I...
Oh.
That's crazy.
Ah!
Not now.
Wow.
But I can't loot it now, though.
What the fuck?
Nope.
That's lava 2.
Of course it is.
Whatever.
Do we have goodies in here?
I don't see any goodies.
Nope.
No goodies.
Shit.
Well, that's the end of that adventure.
This is why you always want to carry around the assembly.
Always.
This one doesn't have anything worth either, does it?
Did I miss anything else here?
I can't believe that happened.
It was so...
I had so much fun!
And then it just got disrupted like that.
Fun disruptor.
What a bummer, man.
Well, the good news is we're going to come back with a better digging machine with a furnace.
Because I've had it.
Living the...
non-netherite life, you know?
I'm going to go get mine.
In fact, maybe I even missed some netherite in these tunnels on my way.
You know, along the walls or something.
Dude.
I'm not leaving until I find my netherite.
You know what that means?
I think you know what that means.
We're going to dig manually until we find one!
I just want one!
I want one!
I'm not fucking leaving.
Wait, maybe it's actually better if I do it like this, right?
And it doesn't matter if I get lost now because that's by design.
I have no torches.
It's the torchless, uh...
netherite session.
Boo!
Give me experience.
Nice.
This way.
Oh!
We're actually almost 30!
Oh my god!
We're going to experiment with, uh...
and chance when we get home and potentially get unbreaking so we can put it on the flyer and then we're going to really go nuts because you know what that means?
It means carrot.
And carrot means night vision which means we're going to come back here with better vision.
Panavision.
Lasers.
Why is there so much light?
Okay, that's lava, of course.
There's so much experience down here, though.
I will say that.
Oh yeah!
We did it!
We found it, baby!
Oh my goodness.
Red alert!
Ancient debris!
Let's see if there's more!
Show me more!
This is ancient debris land.
Okay, guys.
We're going to get two.
Two ancient debris and then we leave.
I didn't expect to find it that fast, you know?
That's unexpected.
Two ancient debris and then we leave.
I mean, you've got to have at least two.
You can't come home with one.
That's just kind of crazy, right?
Okay, that's...
I don't like that.
Get out of there.
Horrible.
Hoi, hoi, hoi.
I can't believe that happened.
My ear is itchy.
Just making sure it's there.
Didn't go anywhere on me.
Let's go this way now.
No.
This way.
Guys, we found the ancient...
Okay, okay.
Wait, wait, wait.
We do three and then we...
Okay, four.
Four.
We do four.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait.
Actually, I'm gonna...
I'm actually gonna preemptively say we do five.
We do five.
How many do I have?
Three.
Oh, you...
Oh, my God.
This is it.
This is...
This is it, man.
This is netherite land.
This way now.
Oh, my goodness.
Oh, okay.
Keep going.
It's fine.
Very nice.
Oh!
Phew!
How?
Okay, I need to...
I need to practice safe session.
This is unsafe session what I'm doing right now.
We need to practice safe session.
Shit balls... I think I'm afraid of some lava.
Why won't that connect?
Okay, fuck this place.
We're gonna go a little this way now.
Soon 30.
Yeah, we can't go home before we're 30, right?
There's no way.
I don't know where I am right now.
Keep looking down.
Dude, I'm actually so excited.
Okay, okay.
A little disappointing.
It's okay.
Nah, it's not disappointing.
We got a lot already.
Okay, I'll take it back.
We go for four.
Four ancient debris.
We're gonna try and put it in the crushing wheel.
Dude!
Imagine.
Cover that up.
Show me the good stuff.
I deserve it.
I've been through hell and everything else to get here.
Can't just let me leave with a measly three, can you?
I need more.
More, more, more, more, more.
In fact, you know what?
I feel like diamond is... for the weak ones now.
Like, I am only netherite now.
Diamond days are over.
I'm a changed man.
Full netherite or bust.
I keep thinking I have a torch, but I don't.
Hopefully, I didn't just make him mad.
By mining that.
Dude, I feel like I should get preemptively excited.
For when it... like, before it happens.
So I preload the excitement.
You know what I mean?
Just to ease the servers of excitement a little bit.
I'm actually just gonna do that.
Oh my god!
It's happening!
I... I see it!
I find... I... Oh, I... I... That's four!
We got four!
Crazy!
Okay, now, when it actually happens...
We can come down a bit more.
You know what I mean?
It's been preloaded.
I don't like blackstone.
I'm sorry.
I said it.
It's kind of ruining the vibe here.
It's too slow.
Then again, you do get to savor all the little emotions.
Netherite does tend to be too quick.
28!
Come on!
We're nearly there.
Also, where the hell am I right now?
How am I even getting out of here?
That's not my problem.
I mean, present problem.
It's gonna be future me problem, but that's fine.
I just know that I have netherite.
That's all that matters.
I feel like I should go back to my lucky area here, where I found a bunch, and keep digging in that area, you know?
This is where I found it.
I think.
It was here.
Let me see if there's more.
In fact, maybe this is the play, to go like this and cover way more.
And it's also easier to see when there's a hole in the floor.
Like there.
There's a hole.
Dude, am I crazy, or is this kind of faster than the machine?
But of course, the machine scales better, you know?
If you put more diggers on it, then it's gonna really scale.
If you put like 88 on it, you're gonna see some serious shit.
Come on, man.
One more.
I swear to God.
On four, I'll stop.
I'll stop on four.
I swear.
Be good to me.
I will not push the...
I will not squeeze the lemon.
I will not go for five.
We do four.
Come on.
I promise.
Just one more.
No.
Okay.
Blackstone and lava?
That's like the stuff of nightmares.
And this bullshit?
Nah, I'm outta here.
I do like this, though.
Yes, give me music.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
I can feel it.
The music is what we need to get to fourth.
The thing is, though...
Ah...
The preloading of the fourth has already been swapped out for something else in my mind.
We may have to preload the excitement again.
Just to make it real, you know?
It's just a fantasy right now, and I want it to become real.
I keep thinking about it, but...
Deep inside, I know it's not really real, right?
I wanna preload the fantasy.
And then I wanna upload the fantasy.
I'm gonna download it, too.
I don't even know what the fuck I'm talking about right now!
I'm so excited for this fourth...
amendment.
Ha ha ha ha!
I don't even know what that is!
What is the fourth amendment?
Is that the one where they...
allow you to...
shoot to kill or something?
That's a thing.
Like, if someone comes on you...
Wait!
Ha ha ha!
I was about to say, if someone comes in your backyard...
and you're like, they're trespassing, you know?
You can just sort of kill them.
That's horrible.
But I guess the other thing is also sort of an assault.
I wonder if that's covered by the fourth amendment.
Wait, how am I not getting any experience?
Oh!
The axe is stealing it!
I felt like I was on 28 forever.
I mean, I also feel like I'm 28 in real life forever, but that's not real either.
To be 28 again.
To be a young lad.
In the rose bushes.
Brother!
I hate this place!
Take me to greener pastures.
Where the milk is fresh.
And the people are sweet.
Cover that up.
Okay, this area, this whole neighborhood here is...
is terrible.
I don't like it.
Let's try this neighborhood.
Mmm, I don't like this guy.
This one feels good.
Come on, one more!
I swear I stop on four.
I stop.
I stop on four.
I will never again squeeze the lime if you let me have one more.
The lime shall forever remain unsqueezed.
I will apply no pressure...
to the lime.
Wait!
Thought I was gonna die.
Imagine dying now.
Fuck that.
Ah!
Oh!
Okay, wait, wait, wait.
One more, but only within a certain radius.
We only check around here.
And if there's nothing?
Then we...
Then we stop.
Okay, but wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
Maybe the radius is big, you know?
It's like a big sphere.
Wait a minute.
Let me...
Let me try something here.
I mean...
We're done.
We stopped.
We are not looking anymore.
Right?
We're not looking right now.
I'm off that.
This is something else now.
I'm just testing something.
Wait a minute.
Hold on.
Dude, it's stealing all my experience.
Can I please get to 30?
Christ.
Yeah.
I'm not looking.
I'm not looking for more.
I just need experience.
Just keep giving me...
The other stuff.
That I don't want, but kind of want.
You know what I mean?
Come on.
Show me.
I need experience.
There we go.
This is what I need.
And then I'll leave.
We're done here.
In fact, even if I find another one...
I'm not even going to take it.
Because I made a pact.
Okay, I'm going to take it, of course.
But...
You know what I mean?
Like, it's the thought that counts.
And I thought that I wouldn't want to take it.
29!
Oh, to be 29 again.
Dude, I swear to God.
When you hit 30, something happens.
And you become like an old fuck.
You start having back problems.
And you're like...
Medically fucked in all kinds of ways.
And you're just...
You got to get up at...
5 in the morning to piss every night.
Like, what is even happening?
It's like something...
A switch flicks in your body at 30, you know?
I hate it.
You used to be able to game through the whole night.
Like, 24 hour sessions.
You can't do that anymore.
Say goodbye to that, you know?
Come on, experience!
Experience!
There we go!
That's what I...
I'm looking for this.
Okay, we're getting more experience.
I'm gonna keep digging.
Wait, this way?
Oh my God, my hand.
Oh!
I'm sweating inside.
Where are we?
No way.
Is this a sign, guys?
I think it's a sign.
It's time.
We're gonna start digging higher up.
Oh my God, not that.
Dude, the problem is...
If I don't find experience for a while...
My pickaxe steals it, you know?
So, I'm kind of forced to stay here a while and keep digging.
And oh, I hate that.
I don't want to do that.
I would hate to do that.
God, I hate digging this right now and looking...
And potentially finding awesome things, but...
I gotta.
I have to.
I just have to do it, you know?
I have no choice.
It's actually out of my hands.
I do like my new, uh...
What the fuck?
Oh my goodness.
How?
Okay, uh...
Okay, new plan.
We're gonna go for N plus 3.
Whatever N is, right now is the amount I have.
So whenever we end up with N plus 3, I stop.
And I mean, I gotta get to level 30, right?
There we go, there we go.
This is what I want.
This is what I really want.
I don't want the other stuff.
La la la la la.
Don't give me the other stuff.
Give me experience.
Mmm, mmm.
Suck it up.
Mmm.
Right in there.
Oh my goodness.
Holy shit.
What the fuck?
What the fuck, bro?
It's a sign.
I think the game wants me to keep going.
It's like a little game, you know?
Like a little tease.
I keep saying I don't want to find it.
Like, I'll stop.
I'll stop.
I promise.
But then it keeps giving me...
And it's like a fun little game we have going here.
I think the game wants me to keep going.
It's not even that I want to keep going.
The game wants me to do it.
And who am I to argue with the game?
You know what I mean?
Look at that!
The game!
Let's keep up the pretense.
The game is good.
The game...
I don't want anymore.
Yes, that's right.
That's right.
I hate it.
Mmm, give me experience.
Come on.
Show me.
Show me the way.
Yes, yes, yes.
Come on.
It's eating all my experience.
That's too bad, isn't it?
Oh, no.
Means I have to stay longer.
The game is being played.
We have a contract.
You feel it?
I'm not even using my mouse with my finger anymore.
I'm using a different finger.
That sounds kind of crazy, doesn't it?
I will...
Okay, okay, okay.
I will stop on the next one.
Wink, wink.
If I get one more wink, wink, I'll stop on the next one.
Shit.
In fact, I'm going to leave it there.
I like light.
Come on now.
You can't stop at 10.
10?
Ha, ha, ha.
I'll stop at the next one.
Plus two.
Wink, wink.
Oh, my goodness.
This is crazy.
I found the Omega place.
Omega.
Oh.
Ha, ha, ha.
Mr. Show me what's good.
Oh.
Yes.
I need to heal my experience bar.
I need to heal my soul.
Give me the stuff.
Guys, we're not leaving until we have a full stack.
I mean, no, no, no.
We're stopping on the next one.
Wink.
Isn't that right, Gabe?
That's right!
We're stopping on the next one.
I stop on the next one.
I will never continue after the next one.
We stop at the next one.
Never again.
This is the very last one.
You hear me, game?
Very last one.
I will never stop.
I mean, I will never not stop.
You know what I mean?
Wink.
Wink, wink, wink.
Show me more.
Okay, that's lava.
We like lava, though.
We like light.
It's a fun little game we're playing.
And we both know what's happening.
We both know!
But do you know?
Do you know what's happening?
I think I have an idea of what you know or may think you know is happening.
What's that sound?
Follow the sound.
It's a sign.
Dude, I found the ultimate holy grail.
This spot I'm in right now.
This is it right here.
Wow.
Adrian.
Where are you?
Show thyself.
Devote thyself to me.
Go on a quest.
See all the buildings.
Eiffel Tower.
Sightseeing.
And what do you find, Brody?
Are you finding what you're looking for?
Because I am.
Okay.
Next one we stop.
For real, though.
For real.
100...
Like, God to heart and hand on...
Whatever, you know?
Like, I stop on next.
The hand goes wherever you want it to go and I'll stop on the next.
Two plus two equals five.
I'll stop on the next.
Getting drunk at five.
I stop on the next.
Oh!
That's the bottom!
We went too deep.
We delved too deep.
But I'll stop on the next.
I didn't like the new helmet.
I don't want to die.
So therefore, I'll stop on the next.
I give him knowing glances.
I'll stop on the next.
Keep digging.
Because we can't stop on the next unless we find the thing that is next.
Isn't that right?
I smell it.
It's here.
Right in here.
Right over here.
In fact, it's up here.
We're actually going up now.
It's unexpected.
It's dangerous.
It's exciting.
Right here.
I swear...
Like, I actually swear.
Rule 12.
12.
I'll stop on the next.
No more.
We stop on 12.
Because it's the rule 12.
And we are on...
You know what?
N plus 1.
But we freeze the N for right now.
You know?
So whatever...
Like, I don't know how many I have right now.
So we're just going to stop on N plus 1.
Frozen N plus...
It's frozen.
So we can't just update it as we go along.
You know?
Like, N is...
It's not a variable.
It's a constant.
But I'm not going to assign a value to it.
Yet.
Because, you know...
Reasons.
Come on.
One more.
Unumas.
This is a legendary run.
You can't stop me like this.
This can't be the end.
As soon as I get one, I'm going to dig straight up.
And I'm going to leave.
Wink, wink.
Come on.
This is not greed.
It's just, you know, following the rules of the game.
I don't even make the rules.
Oh my god.
I'm using my pinky now.
What the fuck, bro?
We're not even finding experience anymore.
Look at our pickaxe.
We will never reach 30.
Hold on.
Sphere and then up.
Okay.
We leave.
I told you I would leave on the next, didn't I?
I'm a man of my word.
We leave.
The question is, where are we?
And how do we get out of here?
Dude, I'm holding the mouse like normally right now.
But it doesn't feel normal.
You know what I mean?
Because it's been like not normal for a while in my hand.
Where is...
Where is out?
I'm leaving.
Like, I'm not even digging.
I'm trying to leave.
Ow.
Well.
Okay, we're going straight up.
Okay, that's a terrible idea.
Especially because there's lava there.
Maybe over here.
Oh, wait a minute.
This is good.
This may be it.
Straight up.
I actually kind of need to focus right now.
This is the most important part of the journey.
There's no way we're right here.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
That's crazy.
Yep.
Guys, did I not tell you?
Did I not...
Where am I?
Wait.
Okay, I guess I go up here.
I've gone up here before.
This looks like a way.
Let's trust past me.
And hold on.
We're not done.
We're not done yet.
Oh, I thought the guy was down there.
Enjoy.
Just going to grab a little extra out the door.
You know, as I leave.
Oh.
Souls.
What?
I can disenchant that.
Nether bricks.
Breakety brack.
I would love a snack.
Calm down, man.
Fucking hell.
Why?
Why is he doing that?
I don't understand.
Like, what's happening?
Yeah, you can have half.
And then the other guys get the other half.
Brother!
Jesus Christ.
I am...
I feel like killing them, actually.
I may kill them.
On my way out.
On my way out, I kill them.
I don't even know what I'm hoping for.
Just something.
I do know what I'm hoping for.
I'm hoping for a carrot.
But I don't think they can drop that for me.
I don't want this shit.
Soul speed!
I'll take that.
That's kind of cool.
I also take these.
And I guess I'll take...
Oh, I actually kind of need this.
Give me that.
Gimme, gimme, gimme.
Gimme more.
Dude, shut up!
Shut up!
Shut the...
Oh my god.
Shut up.
What the fuck?
Guys!
Also, I'm kidding, guys.
Come on.
You thought I...
You thought I threw that away?
Acting.
Ah, come on.
Come on.
I would never do that.
Think I'm crazy or something?
You're crazy.
Um.
Anything else I would like to take here?
Actually, these would be nice.
And this one, too?
I do need iron right now.
I do need string.
That's about it, I think.
Thanks, guys.
Man, what a fucking haul.
Can you believe it?
Hold.
This is like the best day ever.
Oh my god.
Best day ever.
It's like that scene from Pure Ownage, you know?
Where he's going to get breakfast and he has that sort of...
I don't know.
Like, Ontario breakfast or whatever it is.
That's me right now.
I, uh...
I don't even know what to say, man.
This is incredible.
Dude, I thought I lost it.
I have it.
Wow.
Now to remember how to do this.
I think we cook it, right?
That's how that works?
Boink.
I do want to see one thing, though.
Crushing wheel.
No, actually, it's easier if I...
Ancient...
Or, what's it called?
Nether, uh...
Oh, wait.
I guess I need to make it first.
There you go.
Oh!
Let's see what it does.
Okay, we can make the ingot.
Good.
And I guess that's it.
Okay, that's it.
Oh my god.
We need four of these?
That's kind of off the chain, isn't it?
Suddenly, I regret bringing all the gold to the nether.
Why did I give that gold to those pigs?
Terrible.
But we do have some gold.
The first...
Ingot!
Wow.
Oh!
Did you see that?
We're making this.
Chiseled.
Stone bricks.
Oh, that's super easy.
Stone brick slab.
Uh...
How do I make those?
I guess I'll take a stone brick and slab it.
Like that.
Um...
Put that in there.
Slap time!
And then...
Low stone!
What I'm going to do now...
Is I'm going to put this here.
Somewhere.
In here.
Right...
There.
And then... Compass time.
I will never get lost again.
I'm even not gonna name it because I need my experience.
Dude, I... that's like nothing.
Need more gold.
Hoi, hoi, hoi.
Now, I think we gotta turn this diamond pickaxe into the good stuff.
That's a must.
And the way to do that... I think it's this one, actually.
No.
Don't we need, like, a netherite upgrade thingy?
That's a thing.
Boom.
Upgrade... Oh my god, how does that work?
Wait.
Wait a minute.
I don't think we can actually craft one of those.
We have to find it.
Oh, shit.
No.
Oh.
Not like this.
We gotta go back, man.
I don't wanna do that.
The netherite ingot stays here.
That one is super safe here now.
Same as that one.
We got some soul speeds.
Oh, I can this enchant, actually.
Wait.
These leggings are the ones I had before.
This one is pretty good for the nether, actually.
The minus 45% burning time is kind of good.
But check it out.
Maybe we don't need maximum level to find a good enchant for the book for unbreaking.
Wait a minute.
Can I?
Nah, I was wondering.
Maybe I could enchant the thing here, but I don't think I can.
Because, one, it's already enchanted.
And even if it wasn't enchanted, I don't think I can still.
It seemed like there's a memory there in there somewhere saying I can't do that.
So that's unfortunate.
We gotta go back.
Can't believe it.
Put that in there.
Why do I have deployers on me?
How does that work?
Put this in there.
This compass right here is...
a really good one.
In fact, why wouldn't I just make all my compasses do that?
You know what I mean?
Like...
There's no reason to have any compass pointing towards the spawn right now.
I don't need that.
Nobody needs that.
I'm also carrying around this hole for no reason.
Rails...
I would say that's...
Yeah.
Construction.
Oh, I know why I'm carrying the deployers.
Because I disassembled the drilling machine.
I got 20...
Okay.
I think it's all coming back to me now.
I must have disassembled the big drilling machine for some reason.
Wait.
It blew up on the creeper.
I remember now.
I was in...
Not the nether.
I was digging a big, wide...
Hole.
In a mountain.
And the creeper came and ruined it for me.
That's what happened, man.
That was post...
Furnace era.
That's why I have the minecart with Furnace.
That's why I knew the minecart with Furnace wasn't really a minecart with Furnace.
It was all there from the start.
I knew it was different.
Full circle.
This was actually just a big-ass trip to get that memory back.
And now we did it.
We're back where we started.
But not where we started today, but where we started some other day.
But with some extra stuff in the pocket.
That's where we are.
Isn't that wonderful?
I think that was...
That's a good way to end, man.
That's a positive note to end on.
Can you believe my luck?
Today?
It was so over at first, but then it was so...
We're so back.
Couldn't find...
That big area for the life of me.
And then I just went chaotic.
And then I found it.
Insane.
Now to forget it for next day.
No, no.
Because we're going to play soon again.
We're not going to take this big of a break.
Before the next episode.
Although you agreed sick, it's me.
It wasn't me.
I couldn't stop.
Like, my hands did things, you know?
It wasn't me.
I wasn't controlling it.
That's called an addiction.
Not just luck.
You just kept going.
But I didn't, though.
I stopped.
Didn't I?
And think about it like this.
You know that meme of the guy stopping right before the diamonds?
That meme is real.
It's actually a motivational poster.
And this stream was an example of why that is.
You want to keep going.
If I had stopped at one, I wouldn't have had 13.
It's not a gambling addiction meme.
It's telling you to keep digging, man.
You're misunderstanding that one.
Just N plus one more Minecraft stream and I'll stop.
I like your name, SLJ.
When did you make that account?
Oh, I guess you must have made it at least...
Well, 19 months ago.
1.5 years.
I've seen you before, by the way.
Unless you can change your name.
Can you change your name?
When did you change name?
Did I really inspire you at that time to take that name?
You can once.
Aha.
Do gift subs help?
Of course.
You don't even need to sub to help.
You can just watch.
And that's totally cool.
That's all...
That's...
Like, if you just hang out and watch, that's already amazing.
If you want to do gifts up or whatever, that's totally on you.
And you can...
It's going to help, of course, but you don't need to do that.
Not at all.
Thank you, Teflon.
726 of you.
Wait, are you the Teflon?
Are you the Teflon?
I don't remember the number in front of you.
Maybe I just remember your name from somewhere else.
Like, not...
Twitch.
Maybe Discord or something.
Yeah, like, I've seen your name many times.
I just don't remember the number in front.
That's all.
Thank you for the subs, man.
I appreciate it.
You've talked about my name before.
Yeah, yeah, I have.
But I guess I just never noticed the number.
That's all.
The mining trip would be a good video to show to a social studies or something lesson about addiction.
No.
You're getting it all mixed up.
You're getting it inverted.
It's to show that you want to keep going and then know when to stop when a good time to stop is.
Today's stream was actually a display of unreal, um...
What do you call it?
Self-control.
Because think about it.
It was actually me winning.
You know?
Like, I won.
So in hindsight, it was good.
You know what I mean?
Blonde Flower Boy, thank you for the five gifted subs.
And grats to the people who got a sub.
Now you can watch without ads.
You pushed it a bit, though?
Ah, maybe a bit.
Maybe a bit.
But you know, here's the thing.
What you don't know is that I knew that I was quite safe.
I knew that I had plenty of food.
Okay?
I knew that I was very close to the bottom where I could not fall to my death.
So I was actually really, really safe.
Okay?
It was all really calculated.
You see what I mean?
All of this and you didn't reach level 30.
That's true!
That's actually crazy.
Just goes to show how hungry that pickaxe is.
You can't satiate it.
It just wants to keep eating and eating and eating.
Now that's an addiction.
In fact, I'm not addicted.
My pickaxe is...
Completely mastered blocking lava without panicking too.
Exactly, right?
I learned new techs.
I got my memory back.
I learned standing on the rails is a good way to do it.
Hungry Hungry Big Axe.
Dude, that's a great name for the episode.
I'm gonna steal that, Pyrogirl.
That's a great one.
I like that.
I've actually never seen or read Hungry Hungry Hippo.
But I've always wanted to.
Because I keep hearing about it, you know?
All my friends keep talking about it.
Like, every time I see that, I'm like sick of it, you know?
Like, oh fuck, man.
Hungry Hungry Hippo.
It's crazy.
I want some of that.
By the way, the creative music resource pack confirmed works.
Fantastic.
So it was a creative track I heard earlier then.
You can't read Hungry Hungry Hippo?
Why not, Teflon?
How come I can't read it?
Oh, it's a game?
Oh, really?
Wait, what?
I'm afraid to Google it.
I don't know.
I feel like everything's going to be ruined if I Google it.
It's a board game?
Oh, shit.
Maybe that's why they're so obsessed with it, everyone.
Word on the street in Denmark is that there are a lot of backstreet, unsanctioned, Hungry Hungry Hippos tournaments.
I mean, that would explain it, I guess.
When will the train project continue?
The way you just asked that reminds me of...
You know that British meme of...
When are we going to start?
I can't do the voice, but you know what I mean?
If you've seen...
Limmy, you know what it is, right?
So when do we plan to start?
No, we're going to start soon.
The thing is, I just needed...
Here's the thing.
In order for me to get a lot of train time, I need to get train tracks, right?
To get train tracks, I need a lot of iron.
And I also need a lot of stone.
All right?
Now, to get a lot of iron, you need a digging machine.
Okay?
Now, to get a digging machine, I had to go to the nether to retrieve the digging machine.
Little did I know that I already had a digging machine that was better, but that's beside the point.
Now I know.
But I went to the nether to get the digging machine.
Now I have the digging machine.
I came home.
In fact, I have an even better digging machine.
Because I now have the old digging machine with the new digging machine.
And the digging machines combine to make an ultra digging machine.
And we can use that to get iron.
And now we can do Trains next time.
Trains, next time.
When are you playing Geogazer next?
When I play World of Warcraft.
Pretty much.
As soon as I start playing WoW, the servers go down and I play Geogazer.
I haven't even touched World of Warcraft, by the way, since that stream.
I think by now it's probably safe to log in and there's not going to be any issues.
Perhaps I'll do a small stream of that.
Knowing my luck, though, it's going to be another Geogazer stream.
Someone tell me what's going on.
We just finished streaming.
And it was a banger.
Not to toot my own horn here, but I think it was quite good today.
This was a good stream.
I had so much fun.
At least I think it was an amazing stream, because I had so much fun.
There's mods that backport vanilla updates.
Would you be interested in adding backport mods for the latest updates?
I think it's fine the way it is, honestly.
Like, this is cool, you know?
I like this.
As it is right now.
If it works...
Don't change it, right?
This guy does create and deadlock might be peak.
Apparently someone...
Did...
Deadlock?
No, created Minecraft in Deadlock.
I saw something about that on YouTube.
And someone told me about it.
It's funny you should mention those two things.
That's kind of nuts, isn't it?
Exactly.
If it ain't broke, don't fix it.
And the fun right now is peaking, so I want to keep it that way.
Yeah, I know it's a board game now.
The Hungry Caterpillar is a book.
Okay, I haven't heard about The Hungry Caterpillar.
That's a new one to me.
Create and deadlock are the only things I'm playing right now.
Okay.
Well, we're kind of similar then.
Except I just started another game.
Kerbal Space Program.
In fact, the next stream is going to be Kerbal Space Program.
We're going to alternate, I think.
Unless I have, like, a huge urge to do...
One game more than the other.
So, yeah.
Baseline is going to be alternation right now.
It's the Very Hungry Caterpillar.
Important distinction.
Oh, okay.
I guess you said that to...
Teflon there.
Speaking of deadlock, would you do chat lobbies again?
Yes, I would, actually.
I just don't know how many people are playing it nowadays.
Like, I'm actually...
Last time I played, I was having fun doing the ranked.
Haven't actually touched the game since.
But, uh...
I do want to try and get through all the matchmaking.
Or what's it called?
Placement matches?
So I can actually get a proper rank.
I should play Ancestors.
Isn't that a strategy game?
I feel like I've heard of that.
Ancestors.
It may already be on my...
Backlog.
Oh, no, never mind.
What is this?
Are you talking about the Humankind Odyssey?
That's the only thing I found.
By the way, the backlog is here.
It just got a new update.
There's now a watch page where you can go and...
It's basically like...
Well, I'm trying to make it like a better way to...
Browse the series on the channel without going to the YouTube channel.
You can sort under different things and stuff.
Like, if you want to watch something that is within a certain genre or whatever, you know?
Maybe it'll be easier.
I don't know.
I'm gonna add that game to my list then.
Ancestors.
It's gonna take a while for the website to update, though.
Probably like a day.
Let's see here.
Ancestors.
Okay, it has been added to the library.
Thank you for that suggestion.
Did you play the game Satisfactory?
Actually, Utato, I'm going to play Factorio first.
And then I'm gonna play Satisfactory after that.
Because I think it could be fun to try the Factory game in 2D first.
The first one that came.
And then try to see what it feels like to transition from that into 3D.
You know?
Which is what Satisfactory really is.
I am planning on playing it, though.
I saw that Lil Indigestion was playing it.
And he had a lot of episodes on it.
So I imagine he had a lot of fun with it.
So I think I could have a lot of fun with that.
I wanted to bring up Neil.
Fun.
Neil.fun, again, as some fun web games.
Let me see.
Oh, Neil.fun.
I see what you mean.
Oh, it's like a collection of games.
Yeah, maybe.
Maybe it's gonna be another WoW stream where we can't get in.
And we'll do something like that.
I don't think I just want to start a stream and do this.
It's gonna be something we do because we couldn't do something else or something.
That's the idea, I guess.
Yeah, Factorio is amazing.
I played it briefly in the past.
And it seemed very fun.
I had a lot of fun with that.
It's completely changed now, too.
Like, you can apparently launch rockets and shit and go places and expand factories and all kinds of stuff.
Is Iron Nest on your backlog?
I doubt it because I don't even recognize that name.
But, guys, the backlog is already so big.
Are you talking about the heavy turret simulator?
It's the only one I can find.
I'll add it.
Fuck it.
It's on the backlog.
Factorio Space Age is a grind?
I mean, if it's a fun grind, then I don't mind.
You're talking to someone whose favorite game is World of Warcraft.
I mean, I live for the grind.
If the grind is good, right?
So, I don't mind that at all.
Actually, I crave the grind, you know?
I yearn for the grind sometimes.
Live for the addiction.
Well, not addiction.
It's more like...
To me, gaming is like my one and only real big hobby.
And when I don't have World of Warcraft, I don't really have any game that I just sort of play when I don't know what else to do.
You know what I mean?
I love having that type of game that I can just always pull up whenever.
Something that I can put on a YouTube video with on the second monitor or something, and just space the fuck out.
I love that stuff.
Yeah, yeah.
The stream is ending.
Satisfactory, maybe.
The thing is, though, I want to stream that, right?
So I don't want to watch a YouTube video on the other monitor while playing Satisfactory.
It also seems like a game where you maybe have to focus a little bit.
So unless you're a really experienced player, you can't just phone it in, so to speak.
You've got to know what you're doing and learn it.
Another mod to consider adding.
There's a mod that adds Terraria-style sorting.
Like sort inventory and stack items, chest.
Hmm, you know what, Teflon?
I will actually consider that.
I briefly thought about another thing today, which is a simple search in an inventory.
You know, so for example, there's like a little search bar up top.
I click on it, and I go like, I-R-O, and it just highlights everything with iron, you know?
That's something I would like.
Yeah, but I don't want JEI, because it's like a whole-ass new interface that doesn't look vanilla at all.
It doesn't feel good.
I want something just completely native-feeling built into the already existing UI.
Right?
Create has some native ones?
Okay, well...
There you go.
Opus 5.5 just released.
Is it better than Astra, though?
What are the benefits?
Did it actually just release?
And how is it compared to Fable?
What's the music in the background?
It is called...
I think it's called Our Painted Family?
And it's from Expedition 33.
It's an amazing track.
Is this a Minecraft stream?
It was a Minecraft stream.
Maximo.
Because it's ending now in approximately 17 seconds.
It came at the wrong time, I guess.
Right here at the end.
Sorry.
It depends, Swirlfire.
I mean, I like to just hang out a bit after these.
Usually.
Talk about whatever happened today.
In the game.
Alright, I'm actually leaving, guys.
It's time for me to go.
I hope you enjoyed it.
This was a fun return to Minecraft.
What a great one, man.
I can't believe we got that much...
Netherite.
That was mind-blowing.
Holy shit.
It's a new era.
I'll see you next time.
Bye-bye.